Chapter 3: Meeting You In This World

This is...

A little while before the situation with Aki seeking help unfolded, Rio had been flying close to the ground, following the faint traces of footsteps, when he discovered grass that had been heavily trodden on by numerous horses. He came to a stop before the road and immediately deduced that three people had encountered others on horseback. Next, he followed the footsteps with his gaze, then spotted a large convoy of wagons far down the road. The convoy of wagons had stopped, but were about to depart at any moment.

Several exposed wagon loads caught Rio’s eyes. They had several people gathered together on them — slaves, most likely — with swarms of mercenary-like guards surrounding the wagons.

...Slave merchants, huh. This might be bad.

An unpleasant feeling settled in Rio’s chest.

He aborted his flight arts and landed on the ground, before bursting into a sprint toward the wagons, using his enhanced physical abilities. However, he couldn’t just attack them straight away simply because of an unpleasant feeling he had, so he decreased his speed once he had somewhat closed the distance between them. That was when one of the guards noticed Rio.

“Hey, someone’s approaching from the side of the road!” A guard yelled loudly when he noticed Rio, stirring the caution of those around him. Several of the guards immediately drew their weapons and took on a formation to protect the wagons.

“Stop right there!” One of the guards yelled.

Rio decided to demonstrate that he had no hostile intentions, for now. “I’m searching for some people. Three of them. They came from the same direction I did just now.” He explained his intentions without drawing his weapon, staying exactly where he was, as ordered.

The air around the mercenaries changed slightly. They looked at each other, before they all turned to look at a man who was probably the highest-ranked one amongst them.

“...Someone call the boss and the captain over here. Quickly.” The man who was turned to — the leader-like man that Miharu, Masato, and Aki had encountered — said with irritation. Less than half a minute later, a well-dressed man appeared, accompanied by another bulky guard.

“Hmm. So, you’re the one who appeared out of nowhere. What do you want?” he asked unhappily, looking over Rio’s cloaked figure.

“...Forgive me for my rudeness. My name is Hans — you may have heard from your bodyguards already, but I am in search of some individuals. Three people should have appeared from the side of the road a short while ago... Have you seen them?” Rio asked, purposefully choosing to take on a courteous tone toward the haughty man.

However, it was clear that his tone was only for show, as he had given him a fake name he had made up on a whim in case things took a turn for the worst.

“Oh? And here I was, thinking you were but a mere hoodlum...” The well-dressed man muttered, narrowing his eyes.

“No clue. Unfortunately, we’re in a rush. If you’re done here, then leave,” he said with a curt shake of his head.

He had considered the possibility that he was talking to a noble based on Rio’s educated form of speech, but he ultimately decided to feign ignorance.

“I would, but I found the footprints of several people in the grasslands a small distance away from the road. There were signs that the grass had been trampled by horses — fairly recently, too,” Rio said with a troubled smile.

“...Are you accusing us of kidnapping those people?” The well-dressed man asked Rio with an emotionless look.

“Oh, no. Of course not. I was simply hoping you would drop the pretenses and open yourself up to discussion if they really were in your care.” Rio shook his head, wearing a poker face as he selected his words carefully. He had already given them the idea that he was fairly confident, so he tried to make it seem as though he was willing to settle things peacefully by making a roundabout offer to ignore any shady business that they were involved in.

At the same time, he made a show of looking over the wagons that stood behind the man. Unfortunately, there were large numbers of slaves on every wagon; he didn’t know what the people he was searching for looked like to begin with, so all he could do was pass his eyes over each and every one.

“...I’d like to ask you to refrain from staring at my precious cargo so intently. There are many slaves who start feeling a false sense of hope from interacting with outsiders,” the well-dressed man said, glancing at the wagons behind him. He shot the large guard standing next to him a look that said to lower the covers on the wagons. At that, the bulky man and several of his subordinates began to promptly move about.

“H-Help us!” The voice of a young girl echoed from one of the wagons — it was Aki. Nearly everyone present had no idea what Aki had said and what the words meant. Almost everyone, except...

Help... us? Is that... Japanese?

Rio had heard it and understood it. A voice seeking help... But he hesitated for a moment, wondering if he had mistakenly heard wrong. After all, those words shouldn’t have existed in this world.

However, when he turned his gaze toward the wagon that the voice came from, he became certain that he hadn’t misheard.

There, inside the wagon, stood Aki with her East Asian facial characteristics.

“Tch. Cover the cargo already.”

While Rio stood bewildered, the well-dressed man clicked his tongue and quietly ordered his guards to hide the contents of the wagons. He had run out of patience.

Eventually, the covers of the wagons were fully lowered over the interior platforms.

“Now look at what you’ve done. The slaves are making a fuss because of you,” the well-dressed man said, still trying to feign ignorance. On top of that, his words were blunt in order to place the blame on Rio.

“...Please, hold on a moment. The girl who called out just now was one of the people I’m searching for. She was asking for help... Could you explain what’s going on here?” Rio asked in a composed tone after calming down and returning to his senses. He wasn’t going to back down, either.

The well-dressed man’s expressions twisted in displeasure. “What a bother. Enough already. Kill him,” he ordered the bulky guard next to him in irritation.

“You heard the boss, people! We’re going with the simplest and easiest way of silencing someone. Form up!”

With a grin, the guard stirred up the men surrounding them. The mercenaries got in formation gleefully and enclosed Rio in an instant.

Their movements were a fine show of leadership — the skill of a mercenary group varied dramatically depending on the abilities of their commander, but all the mercenaries here seemed to be quite experienced in group combat. “You’ve mistaken foolishness for bravery, as there’s a time and place for this kind of thing. This isn’t it. Any last words? If you beg for your life and agree to become a slave, then I may be willing to spare you. You do have a nice face, after all... Any interest in selling your body?” The well-dressed man asked in triumphant arrogance, obviously feeling assured in his overwhelmingly advantageous position.

“...How repulsive. You should have just handed over the people you kidnapped without a fuss while you could. However, if this is what you want, I won’t hold back, either,” Rio said in a calm but deadly tone, shaking his head in annoyance.

The man reacted to the bloodlust directed toward him. “E-Enough. Kill him!” he ordered in a high-pitched voice.

“Get him!” The bulky commander of the mercenary squad ordered the soldiers surrounding Rio.

The mercenaries thrust their spears at Rio from every direction as they protected themselves with their shields, but Rio gracefully leaped into the air and out of the circle of attack with ease.

“Wha...?!” The mercenaries were taken aback in spite of themselves, staring after Rio dumbfoundedly as he cleared their heads with a light jump.

“Eek?!” Rio pulled the dagger hidden under his overcoat out while mid-air, equipped it in his left hand, then stabbed at the legs of the mercenaries nearby without hesitation as soon as he landed. The men who had been stabbed let out a scream.

Will they lose their fighting edge, now? Rio thought. Then, suddenly —

“Photon Projectilis!” The commander of the mercenary squad fired offensive magic toward Rio. A magic circle floated before the left hand he had held up toward Rio, his magic essence turning into high-speed bullets of light energy that shot forth in rapid succession.

Rio dashed to the side and evaded the attack.

...He’s awfully calm. Worthy of being the leader to all these mercenaries, I suppose. Guess it wouldn’t be that easy, Rio thought tiredly as he accelerated.

“Our opponent is using physical ability enhancement! Keep him moving and strike when he’s fatigued! Get into a defensive formation!”

The commander calmly called out directions as he relentlessly fired his light bullets at Rio. With that, the other mercenaries regained their composure, too.

The mercenaries got into a close formation, protecting the well-dressed man and the commander as he fired his offensive magic. Then, they lowered their bodies with their shields fortified in a circle so that the commander’s trajectory was unobstructed.

Rio had been avoiding the bullets by darting freely through the wide field next to the road, but when he saw the sight of the mercenaries, he frowned in irritation and charged toward the wall of shields head-on.

“The fool lost his patience. Ready the spears!” A bloodthirsty grin made its way across the commander’s face.

While the lethality of Photon Projectilis was low, it had enough force to severely wound a regular human. The magic also allowed for the ability to continuously produce rapid-fire bullets at will once activated. Its accuracy was low against opponents moving from left to right, but that changed dramatically when the opponent approached directly from the front. To charge straight for the defensive formation of shields was the height of foolishness.

The light bullets fired from the commander were closing in on Rio.

“Wha?!” For the briefest moment, the image of Rio’s form in the mercenaries’ vision blurred. The rush of light bullets pierced through empty space, or so they had thought.

“...Huh?”

Before they realized it, Rio had traveled around the mercenaries and drawn his sword, holding it aloft sideways. The sword glowed, then released an explosive blast of wind.

“Gah?!” When Rio swung his sword, the shield-wielding mercenaries were cleanly blown away into the distance. With the wall protecting him gone, the commander took in a breath and moved to draw his sword reflexively.

However, he was already too late.

Rio closed in on him instantly, then moved his sword almost in slow motion as he stabbed the commander precisely through the solar plexus.

“Tch?!”

The commander’s eyes widened in shock, his expression showing he didn’t understand what had happened at all. When Rio withdrew his sword and slowly stepped back, the commander reached down to slowly touch the wounded area. Seeing that his hands were dyed red, the commander realized his imminent death.

With that, he feebly collapsed to the ground.

Rio tightened his grip around his bloodied sword shamefully before immediately turning his gaze to the well-dressed man, who stood frozen and in a daze.

“Ah...?!” The man let out a soundless shriek when his eyes met Rio’s. He instinctively tried to back away, but lost his balance in his rush and fell on his backside.

Rio thrust his bloodstained blade at the man and looked down. “Release the children you kidnapped,” he ordered in a cold voice.

The man let out a pathetic sound. “Eek!”

“The others won’t move unless you order them to, right? Hurry up,” Rio said, sighing in irritation.

“R-Release them now! Quickly!” the man yelled in a fluster, and the frozen mercenary guards jumped into action.

In that time, Rio wiped the blade of his sword and fastened it to his belt unsheathed. Then, he grabbed the well-dressed man by the neck and roughly dragged the corpse of the commander to the side of the road with his other hand.

“Eek! W-Why me?! What are you going to do?!” he wailed as he looked at the body of the commander with a paled expression.

“This guy’s dead body was just in the way. And you’re a hostage,” Rio said, lightly flinging the corpse of the commander into the grass; now the body could no longer be seen from the road. Grabbing his sword in his newly freed right hand, Rio and the man then returned to the road.

The mercenaries were silently gathered at the road, but they fearfully retreated when Rio approached. They were aware from the previous battle that the difference in their abilities was too great, and now, their commander was dead and their client taken as a hostage. They had completely lost the will to fight.

Aki and Masato had just been safely released from the wagon and were standing a small distance away from the mercenaries. Rio approached the two and spoke to them awkwardly in Japanese.

“...Are you two the only ones that are safe?”

“Y-You can understand us?!” Aki asked, clinging to his words.

“I can, but... I’ll leave the details for later. I thought there was one more of you. Was I mistaken?” Rio asked hesitantly.

Aki nodded with vigor. “T-There is! She was taken to another wagon!”

Rio looked down at the well-dressed man he had grabbed with his left hand. “I don’t see the last person. Which wagon is she in?” he asked, casually showing the sword held in his right hand.

“T-The second to last wagon on the right side! She’s on that one!”

“...You haven’t done anything to her, have you?”

“I-I haven’t! I haven’t done anything!” he replied frantically to Rio’s questions.

“I’m going to check. You’re coming with me,” Rio said, dragging the well-dressed man with him.

“I’m going to save your friend. Will you follow me?” he called out to Aki and Masato.

The two of them looked down at the completely terrified slave merchant with something like pity before hesitantly nodding. “Y-Yes!”

Once they arrived at the wagon where Miharu was, Rio turned to the slave merchant. “It seems to be locked.”

The door to the platform of this wagon was far more securely locked than the others.

“I-I have custody of the key to this wagon.”

“Then open it already,” Rio ordered, releasing the slave merchant from his grip around the neck.

The man stood up in a fluster and tried to unlock the wagon door with his trembling hands; after fumbling for a bit, the door to the wagon’s interior platform was finally unlocked.

“Don’t try anything clever,” Rio warned him with a sharp look before opening the unlocked door. A dark and gloomy air permeated the interior.

◇◇◇

With a dull, grinding creak, the door to the interior of the wagon opened. Light from outside filtered through to the interior of the covered platform, replacing the stale body odor with fresh air.

Miharu looked up at the opened door worriedly... But it wasn’t just her. The wagon was packed full of beautiful young women whose gazes were hesitantly drawn toward the door, when a boy with an androgynous face appeared. They all stared at Rio.

When he felt the gazes of all the girls locked on him at the same time, he began to look around the platform somewhat uncomfortably. Like everyone else, Miharu was also observing Rio’s face.

Is he looking for someone... Huh?! Miharu flinched when their eyes met.

As Rio looked at her, engrossed, Miharu stared back in a daze. She felt like she was being sucked into his eyes. The two of them continued to watch each other in silence; Rio remained so still, it was almost like time had stopped. The same could be said about Miharu, too.

“...” Rio muttered something Miharu couldn’t make out, his eyes watery and face twisting as though he was about to cry as he looked at her. Then, for some reason, Miharu felt like she wanted to cry, too.

Even though she was meeting him for the first time, there was a sense of nostalgia that couldn’t be described rising within her chest.

After some time, Rio’s expression changed to one that looked rather guilty. He sheathed the sword in his right hand as though to hide it, before taking a hesitant step onto the platform. He approached Miharu nervously. “I’ve come... to save you,” Rio said gently to Miharu with an awkward smile.

◇◇◇

Rio slowly offered his hand out to Miharu, who sat on the floor of the platform.

“T-Thank you very much.” Miharu’s eyes widened in awe before she timidly took Rio’s hand while watching his expression. He grasped her hand with reservation.

He noted how soft her hand was; unlike his rugged hands covered in sword blisters, her hand was pale, delicate, and fair. A vast difference to the hands that had just killed a man.

Ayase Miharu... It really is Mii-chan. Why is she here in this world? Rio’s face almost twisted with the indescribable emotions within him. Unable to look at Miharu directly, he avoided her gaze, his expression laden with guilt.

He had always wanted to see her again — yet now that she was here before him, he felt absolutely terrified. He had become a different person than Amakawa Haruto. He could no longer return to his former self, because he felt like he had been stained with sin.

It was true — Rio had already killed someone with his own hands, and he had set off from the Yagumo region carrying an intensely burning desire for vengeance.

He let go of Miharu’s hand. “Your two acquaintances are waiting outside. Let’s go,” he said, turning on his heel.

“U-Umm... What about them?” Miharu asked him timidly as she watched the girls around her stare with envy. Rio shook his head with a troubled expression.

“While you and your friends were kidnapped, these girls are most likely here after going through the proper legal procedures for a slave trade. If I take them along with me, I’ll become a criminal.”

Slaves were people without rights. By law, they were treated as objects. That was why stealing them was considered theft, carrying out a scam for them was fraud, and snatching them was robbery or extortion.

“T-That can’t be...” Miharu looked around at the girls in a daze.

“I’m sorry. I can’t do anything...” Rio’s expression darkened apologetically.

“N-No! It’s not your fault! I’m the one who should be sorry!” Miharu regretted her own foolishness keenly, and her own expression turned to one of embarrassment.

“Let’s go.” Out of consideration for Miharu, Rio held her hand as he urged her to move. She allowed herself to be led out of the wagon.

“There’s a bit of a step to the ground, so watch your feet.” Rio stepped out of the wagon before Miharu, then moved to help her down.

“O-Okay. Thank you very much.” Miharu timidly stepped out of the wagon. Then, suddenly, Aki ran over and hugged her.

“Miharu!”

“I’m so glad you two are safe.” Miharu gently patted Aki on the back. Masato stood next to the two of them and look on bashfully.

I’m glad too, truly. So... that voice was talking about Mii-chan... right?

Rio also smiled in relief. But at the same time, he found it mysterious that the voice in the back of his head had known Miharu and the others would appear here.

That being said, there was no use wondering about that now.

Imagine if I hadn’t made it in time... It gives me goosebumps just thinking about it. All because of this guy... Rio directed a quiet but murderous gaze at the slave merchant.

“Eek?!” The merchant backed away in fear.

For a moment, Rio considered taking the slave merchant’s life, too, but he restrained himself — he couldn’t let his impulses drive him to murder without considering the consequences. Most importantly, he didn’t want Miharu and the other two to see any dead bodies, much less the sight of himself killing someone.

“Did they steal anything from the three of you?” Rio asked Miharu, Aki, and Masato with a sigh.

“Umm, they took our bags...” Miharu answered on everyone’s behalf.

Rio immediately turned to the slave merchant. “Where are their belongings?” he asked.

“T-They’re in my wagon! I’ll return them, I’ll return them right away! Just wait there!” The slave merchant responded in a flurry, then ran toward his own wagon. Less than a minute later, he returned and thrust several bags out at Rio.

“And everything is still inside, right?” Rio questioned the slave merchant in a cold voice. He passed the belongings over to the three without pause.

“O-Of course! I haven’t touched a thing! I-I’ll give you money, too, so please believe me!” The slave merchant nodded furiously, then held out a small pouch that was sagging with coins.

Rio accepted the pouch and took a peek; there was indeed a significant amount of gold coins inside. It was probably intended as some kind of compensation for what they had gone through.

“Is there anything missing from your bags?” Rio asked.

“No. Everything’s here,” Miharu, Aki, and Masato replied quickly.

“You don’t seem to be lying.”

“Yes, that’s what I said! Please believe me, I beg of you!” The slave merchant pleaded desperately.

“...All right. But if you ever try to do something to them again, I’ll find you and kill you,” Rio threatened.

“I got it, I got it!” The slave merchant nodded in fear.

With that, Rio had nothing more to say to him. “Let’s get away from this place, first and foremost. I’ll lead you to somewhere safe,” Rio said, starting to walk and prompting Miharu and the others to hesitantly follow him.

Once the entire group had walked out of sight, the slave merchant fell to his knees, feeling as though his soul had left his body.

◇◇◇

Rio and the others headed down the road toward the north, with Miharu, Aki, and Masato silently following him from afar.

There was no conversation between the four of them. Every now and then, Rio would turn to check on them, but he wasn’t sure what to say as an awkward air fell between them. Miharu and the other two also seemed nervous, not quite understanding the reality of their situation, and remained silent in somewhat of a daze. Thus, the silence continued as they walked on with a healthy distance maintained between them.

“Pretty...” Aki suddenly murmured. Her gaze was drawn toward the west — the day was nearly over as the sunset dyed the horizon scarlet red. It was scenery that couldn’t be seen in Japan.

The rest of the party naturally turned to the western sky.

“U-Umm, I’m sorry. Excuse me?” Miharu timidly spoke to Rio’s back.

“Erm, what is it?” Rio flinched before awkwardly turning around.

“Thank you very much for saving us,” Miharu said, finding the courage to speak up. She bowed her head at Rio. “Who knows what may have happened to us if you hadn’t come.”

It was a gesture that clearly conveyed the sincerity of her gratitude and her proper, educated upbringing.

Rio looked at Miharu sadly. “No, I only did what should have been done. There’s a lot I want to ask you, too,” he said, shaking his head uncomfortably. Miharu slowly raised her head.

“Umm, my name is Ayase Miharu. May I ask your name? Also, umm... If it’s possible, we’d like to ask you some things too.”

“My name? My name... Because of some circumstances, right now my name is Haruto... I don’t have a family name.” For a moment, Rio was shaken, and he averted his eyes in hesitation. However, he decided on telling them the alias he was officially operating under while moving around in the Strahl region.

Rio was a wanted criminal after formerly being falsely convicted in the Kingdom of Beltrum, so he figured it would be better to change his name. Black hair also stood out in the Strahl region, so he had changed its color with a magic artifact. That was why his hair was currently gray.

His moment of hesitation was due to the sense of resistance he felt toward calling himself “Haruto” in front of Miharu. That being said, calling himself Rio would have required a more complicated explanation.

In the end, acting so uncertain about giving his name would have seemed suspicious, so Rio resolutely called himself Haruto. Then, he turned to watch Miharu for her reaction.

“Haru...to?” Miharu blankly murmured Rio’s alias — no, Rio’s former name.

“Haruto?” Aki also showed a conflicted expression. The tone of her voice almost sounded bitter.

“Aki-chan,” Miharu said. Aki looked at her in surprise, but Miharu simply shook her head in silence.

...Aki? Rio’s eyes widened after hearing Aki’s name. That name was the same as Amakawa Haruto’s little sister; the one his mother had taken away when their parents divorced.

Rio examined Aki’s face. She was only four years old the last time he had seen her, and the impact of noticing Miharu first had distracted him, but she certainly did bear a resemblance. But, the most conclusive bit of information was in how Miharu had called her Aki.

“...Umm, what is it?” Aki asked Rio timidly, noticing that she was being stared at.

“Ah, no. Sorry. I was just wondering if there was something wrong with my name.” Rio stifled his unease and pasted on a smile.

“I’m sorry. It’s nothing,” Aki apologized, seemingly ashamed.

“Hey, what do you mean you don’t have a family name, Haruto? Ah, I’m Sendo Masato. Aki’s little brother.” Masato, who had been listening quietly, introduced himself.

“Sendo, brother... Then, Aki would be Sendo Aki — is that right?” Rio asked Aki.

Masato had said he was Aki’s little brother, but their family name wasn’t Amakawa and Amakawa Haruto didn’t have a little brother that could have been this old. Since that was the case, Rio immediately assumed Masato was a child of the person his mother must have remarried to.

“Ah, yes. That’s right. Sorry, I didn’t introduce myself earlier.” Aki nodded, bowing her head at Rio.

Rio looked up at the sky in thought. “It’s fine... Masato, you asked why I don’t have a family name, right? The sun’s about to set, and we’ll be talking for a while, so let’s move somewhere else first. I’ll set up a place where we can relax. Come this way,” Rio said, moving into the grasslands next to the road.

Miharu, Aki, and Masato looked at each other before nodding and following him.

Rio continued to progress further and further into the empty grasslands, and the others gradually became uneasy following him, wondering where they could relax in a grassy field like this.

Rio looked around the darkening field curiously before giving the three a strained smile. “Around here should do,” he muttered.

The place they had arrived at had flat ground, and was a fair distance away from the road — unless someone was staring attentively from the road, it was an area that couldn’t be easily spotted.

“Wait just one moment... I’ll prepare it right now,” Rio said, before placing his hands against the ground and manipulating the dirt to make a stable foundation. To Miharu, Aki, and Masato watching him from the side, however, it was unclear as to just what he was doing.

“Dissolvo.”

Rio held out his left hand equipped with the Time-Space Cache and chanted the activation spell. In the next moment, the space before his eyes distorted greatly, twisting like a vortex. Then, it was over in the next instant, leaving a huge rock house in its wake.

“W-What in the world...?” Aki muttered in utter shock. Miharu and Masato were standing there looking at the rock building in astonishment.

Rio smiled at their reactions. “It looks like a regular old rock, but the interior is a nice living space. Come this way,” he said, walking over to the door with familiarity.

Miharu and the others remained where they were, staring at Rio’s back and the stone house in shock. Rio invited them inside once more.

Chapter 4: Explaining The Circumstances

Miharu, Aki, and Masato all held their breath in unison after Rio stepped into his rock house.

The sight of a spacious living and dining area brightly illuminated by magic artifacts greeted the three. In the corner of the room was a staircase that led to the second floor.

“Please, have a seat on that sofa,” Rio said, then went to the kitchen alone and prepared several drinks and wet towels. Rio’s guests sat on the sofa nervously and looked around the room in wonder.

“Here you are — you must be thirsty. There’re seconds if need be, so don’t hold back.” Rio handed them three metal mugs filled with iced tea.

“T-Thank you very much.” Miharu gratefully accepted the drink. They had been walking through the arid grasslands with only a small amount of food and water rationed between them the whole time, so having the issue of dehydration solved was a huge relief.

“Thank you, Haruto! I was really thirsty... More, please!” Masato said, having gulped down the drink before immediately requesting another with sparkling eyes.

“...Have a little restraint. Geez,” Aki muttered to Masato with an exasperated look.

“It’s fine. Seeing someone drink that enthusiastically makes it worth it. But your stomach will feel cold if you drink it too fast, so be wary of that. Or, there’s hot tea instead,” Rio said with a smile, pouring iced tea into Masato’s mug.

“I’m sorry. My brother has no manners... Thank you very much.” Aki bowed her head timidly before putting her mug to her lips. Like the others, she was thirsty, too, and her mug was soon drained.

Without a moment’s delay, Rio refilled her mug; Aki blushed with embarrassment and thanked him again, this time taking her time to enjoy the flavor.

Meanwhile, Miharu was watching Aki and Masato eagerly drink their tea with a smile on her face, before bringing her own mug to her mouth.

After everyone replenished themselves and took a breather, Rio looked straight at Miharu, who sat across from him. “Can you tell me why the three of you were in a place like that?” he asked.

The three of them looked at each other before Miharu answered on the behalf of the other two. “Actually, we don’t even know ourselves. We just found ourselves standing in a field with no idea as to what was going on...”

“I see. So that means you don’t know where you are, right?”

“Yes, I have no idea. Umm, where exactly are we...?”

“The Strahl region in the continent of Euphelia. If I told you you were in a field near the border between the kingdoms of Galarc and Centostella... Would that ring any bells?”

“T-They’re all names I’ve never heard of before. We’re not in Japan, are we?” Miharu asked with all her remaining hope, her expression darkening with worry.

“Unfortunately not.” Rio shook his head apologetically.

“T-Then where are we? Somewhere in Europe?” Aki asked impatiently.

“...I’m sure that you have witnessed all kinds of spectacles over the course of today. Do you really believe you’re still on Earth?”

“That’s... T-Then where are you saying we’ve ended up? And who are you, anyway? Why can you speak Japanese?” Aki asked, worriedly, in a rougher voice. She didn’t seem to want to face reality.

“...At the very least, it isn’t Earth. The name of the place is as I told you just now. Also, the reason why I can speak Japanese... is probably because I used to be Japanese, maybe?” Rio shrugged as he answered with a bitter smile.

“Eh...?” Aki and the others were taken aback.

...The three of them don’t know anything... about this world, or why they came to a world like this. It’s just like me, when I woke up nine years ago with my memories of my previous life. No... they’re even more clueless than I was. At least I had my memories as Rio... Rio watched Miharu, Aki, and Masato with a sorrowful expression.

“U-Umm, what does ‘used to be Japanese’ mean...?” Miharu asked Rio timidly.

“It means exactly that. Maybe if I called it my ‘previous life’ instead...? You may not believe me, but I have memories from another life... The life when I was a university student in Japan.” Rio averted his gaze uncomfortably as he answered.

“Erm...” Miharu, Aki, and Masato were at a loss for words, unsure of how to respond to that.

“At any rate, I don’t have any objective proof of formerly being Japanese, but that’s why I can speak Japanese, so I would appreciate it if you could just take that at face value. More importantly, don’t you want to know what happened to the three of you?” Rio gave a vague smile before quickly changing the subject.

“H-Hey, Haruto. Does that mean we’ve come to a fantasy RPG world? It’s a world with swords and magic, right?” Masato asked rather eagerly.

“I never played those kinds of games in my previous life, so I’m not quite sure, but I believe it’s something like that. But unlike a game, there’s no reset button here,” Rio replied with a strained smile.

“Would we have been in pretty big trouble if you hadn’t come along, Haruto?” Masato asked in a cold sweat.

“...Yeah, you would’ve been made into slaves at that rate,” Rio told them stiffly and curtly.

“N-No way... Slaves...?” Aki murmured in a daze.

A pained expression fell over Miharu’s face, but her shock wasn’t as great as Aki’s.

“What do you mean by ‘slaves’?” Masato questioned dubiously.

Aki looked at Masato in exasperation. “Y-You don’t even know that?”

“I-I don’t. I’m bad at language and vocabulary. Do you know what it is, Aki?” Masato asked her sullenly.

“O-Of course I do. A slave is... Uhh... Umm...” Aki tried to explain the concept of slavery, but found herself at a loss for words. While she knew the general meaning of the word, she couldn’t explain it very well.

Miharu had a conflicted expression, too.

“Simply put, a slave is someone treated as an object instead of a human,” Rio interrupted.

“...Treated as an object?” Masato cocked his head, not quite grasping the concept.

“Maybe you’d understand it better if I said it this way: it’s the buying and selling of people, like animals. The person sold becomes the property of the person who bought them, so they have to do what they say.”

“H-Hah?! Isn’t that basically a pet?! And you’re saying that almost happened to us? How could they do such a thing?!” Masato yelled with rage, finally understanding the meaning.

“Black hair is unusual, and you look neat and tidy. Although you can’t understand the language here, it’s clear you had a good upbringing... So they probably assumed you would sell for a fairly high price.” Rio gave his assumption in a serious tone.

Masato paused to take a breath. “...How could they do such a thing?! And the buyers, too... How horrible! What’s so great about treating people like that? We’re not dolls!” he said in a high pitched voice. For someone raised in a modern society, slavery was an evil violation of human rights.

“Well, the buyers have their own reasons for buying. Whether its fun or not aside, there are those who simply buy them because they’re a convenient way to get labor done...” Rio said, troubled.

He had already thrown away the morals he had as a modern Japanese person and accepted the necessity of a slavery system in their current society; that was why Masato’s anger toward slavery didn’t really stir him. At the same time, he hoped that his guests didn’t have the same morals as his own jaded ones.

“What’s... with that...” Unable to accept the truth, yet faintly aware that it was pointless to continue lamenting over it, Masato hung his head limply.

“...Let’s get back on topic. Have the three of you accepted the reality that you’ve come to a different world that isn’t Earth?” Rio smiled helplessly and focused his eyes on Miharu, who sat directly opposite him.

“...Yes,” Miharu nodded seriously. There were too many aspects that couldn’t be explained otherwise, and while she didn’t want to accept it, she had no other choice.

“Naturally, you want to go back to Earth... right?” Rio asked carefully.

Aki stood up eagerly. “W-We can go back?!” she asked.

“Calm down,” Rio said, silencing Aki. “My question was badly worded — I don’t know whether or not you can return, but I don’t think it should be impossible to achieve...” He shook his head apologetically.

“O-Oh. I’m sorry. I jumped the gun...” Aki apologized awkwardly.

“I don’t know why the three of you are here in this world. However, the location I believe you arrived at when you first came to this world had evidence that time-space sorcery was used — I was only able to notice your presence because I had detected those traces of time-space sorcery. That is why I believe the three of you were purposefully summoned into this world,” Rio explained.

“Time-space sorcery... you say?” Miharu repeated the words she was unfamiliar with in question.

“Yes. In this world, there exists a technique called sorcery. Sorcery cannot be explained by science. For example, the house I brought out in this grass field was stored through time-space sorcery.”

“So that’s what that was...”

“In order to use sorcery, a formula needs to be drawn and have essence poured into it. It’s a little hard to explain through words, so I’ll show you an example.”

As Rio explained, he picked up one of the quills that was placed on the table and began to draw a simple geometric pattern on some paper. Miharu, Aki, and Masato watched on curiously as he drew.

“This is a very basic formula. When I pour magic essence into it...” After finishing the formula several seconds later, Rio placed his hand against it and released his essence. The formula on the paper absorbed the essence, melding with mana to cause a world-altering phenomena.

Immediately afterward, a bubble of water several centimeters in diameter formed above the formula. The bubble then followed the laws of gravity and fell down, soaking the paper the formula was drawn on.

“A world-altering phenomena occurred and created water from nothing. That was elementary water sorcery, but by combining an endless number of possible formulas, you could control fire, create ice, form electricity, and all kinds of other phenomena.” Rio gave the minimum explanation before demonstrating it to them; they widened their eyes in shock at the sight of the soaked paper.

“W-Wow! That’s amazing, Haruto! So this is sorcery!” Masato was the first to snap to his senses and yell in excitement.

“Shut up — you don’t have to be so loud about it,” Aki said, expressing her disapproval at the noise from where she sat on the other side of Miharu.

“But, Aki... Did you see that just now?! Water appeared out of nowhere. This is sorcery! Sorcery!” Masato brushed off Aki’s scolding and innocently displayed how happy he was, which was quite apparent.

“It’s not as surprising compared to a house appearing in the middle of a field,” Aki said sullenly.

Miharu watched the two of them with a smile. “Right. Like Aki-chan said: this is no big deal when compared to how I made the rock house appear out of nowhere. That was time-space sorcery. I’m sure you can at least imagine how difficult it is to interfere with time and space?”

“...Yes. There’s no way anyone could do that normally.” Aki nodded with suspended disbelief.

“That understanding is pretty much the same even in this world, where sorcery is widespread. Actually, time-space sorcery is a technique that has yet to have any chance of being practically implemented. There’s a lot of variation in the types and difficulty of time-space sorcery, as well as exceptions like the one I showed you,” Rio said, emphasizing the difficulty of time-space sorcery. His goal was to make it clear how abnormal it was that they were summoned to this world in such a way.

“What do you mean by that? Everything you say is so confusing... I don’t really get it.” Masato cocked his head in confusion.

Rio simplified his words and gave a wry smile. “I believe the three of you were summoned to this world through time-space sorcery, but to recreate that sorcery to send you back to Earth would be almost impossible using the current state of sorcery in this world... Does that make sense?”

“I still don’t get it. Are you saying we were summoned with sorcery that no one in this world can use? Even though it’s sorcery that exists in this world?” Masato’s doubts were most justified.

“A lot of the knowledge about sorcery was lost in a war of the gods that occurred over a thousand years ago. The sorcery of that time was far more advanced than what we have right now. I believe the time-space sorcery that brought the three of you to this world was from that time,” Rio replied, feeling impressed at how direct Masato’s question was.

“A war of the gods... I see. If that’s how it is, then I can understand.” Masato seemed to be excited about something.

Aki sighed. “...You enjoy things like that, after all. I envy how simple-minded you are,” she murmured under her breath, her voice fading out toward the end. While it wouldn’t have been hard to believe all of this back on Earth, here, her brain was finally feeling tired.

Maybe we should stop here for now? The more complex stuff can be dealt with step-by-step later.

Rio realized with a wry smile that the most adaptable person in this group might just be the youngest, Masato.

“For now, that’s all I have on the reason why I think the three of you were brought to this world. With no obvious clues, we’ll have to dig further to find any evidence about how you can go back to Earth. Do you have any questions?” he asked, wrapping up their discussion.

“...Umm, actually... Just before we came to this world, we were in a group of five. Do you know if there are any traces of the other two being nearby?” Aki asked hesitantly.

“I don’t believe there was any other disrupted essence located in the area, but... if you were together, then the other two must have been near you, right?” Rio asked in contemplation.

“Yes. We were meeting up together after school and were just standing around and chatting.”

“Did anything abnormal occur? If time-space sorcery activated, then it would have looked like the air was being distorted.”

“Onii-chan... I was talking to my brother when it looked like he suddenly distorted, right before my eyes,” Aki answered slowly, thinking back to her memories.

“Your brother...” For a moment, Rio’s heart skipped a beat thinking she was talking about him, but immediately realized they were children from his mother’s remarriage.

“Umm, I was talking to an upperclassman named Satsuki when she looked like she distorted. I may have been seeing things, but it looked like the distortion closed in around us, too,” Miharu explained, hesitantly recounting what she had witnessed herself.

“...And the same happened to you, Aki?”

“Y-Yes. It was only for a second so I wasn’t sure, but it was like a distortion that started from my brother grew larger and swallowed us...?” Aki tilted her head.

Rio analyzed their descriptions. Normally, the point of distortion starts from the target of the time-space sorcery. Based on what these two have said, the sorcery was activated separately, with this Satsuki person and Aki’s brother as the focus point, he thought.

“If it’s exactly as Miharu witnessed, then I believe there’s a high chance that those two were also summoned into this world through time-space sorcery,” Rio concluded.

Aki’s expression brightened immensely. “R-Really?!”

“Probably. If anything, those two were probably the ones summoned, while the three of you were dragged along for the ride. The reason why you were separated from the other two may be because the two time-space sorceries interfered with each other at such a close distance and messed up your teleportation coordinates, or something,” Rio replied, his expression darkening in stark contrast to Aki’s.

“B-But that still means my brother is somewhere in this world, right?”

Aki sought for the answer she wanted to hear; it was clear she admired her brother a great deal. The way she pleaded was almost as though she had found a ray of hope within a situation of utter despair.

“...I can’t be certain, but the possibility is most certainly there,” Rio answered vaguely with a troubled look.

While he believed there was a very high chance that that was the case, as long as he didn’t know what kind of time-space sorcery was used, he couldn’t afford to give her a confident answer. Not to mention that it seemed as though Aki had yet to realize that just because the other two were summoned into this world didn’t mean they were safe.

However, there was no need for him to agitate her concerns any further. After all, they first had to focus on solving the problems that were right in front of them.

“I know there’s still so many things you don’t understand yet, but for now, let’s think about how you’re going to survive from now on. I will help you as much as I can, so you can leave all your food and shelter needs to me for now and focus on learning the language and knowledge of this world.” Rio pulled together the biggest smile he could muster.

“A-Are you sure?” Miharu asked timidly. She carefully watched Rio’s face.

No matter how optimistic she tried to be, it was impossible for them to live in this world without knowing the language. In order to survive, they had to rely on Rio. Miharu had actually planned on requesting his assistance herself, but she was more than aware of how shameless the proposal to raise three strangers was, so she had been finding it difficult to approach the topic and bring it up.

“Yes. There is one condition I’d like you to follow, though, so as long as you abide by that...” Rio said in a light tone to avoid making them feel wary.

“A condition?”

“There’s no need to be nervous about it. It’s just that I’m a bit of a peculiar individual, with my memories of my previous life and all. You’ll see and hear a lot of absurdities about me as we live together, and I’d like you to keep all of that secret from outsiders, unless you have my permission. For example, the existence of this house. However, if it seems like your safety will be put in danger, I won’t mind if you divulge any information. What do you think?”

Miharu was rather taken aback. “E-Erm, is that all? Are you sure? You’d be looking after three people.”

All the burden would be on Rio this way, with practically nothing asked of Miharu, Aki, and Masato. The proposal was far beyond anything Miharu and the others could have hoped for, when they had no other choice than to rely on Rio. The one-sidedness of Rio’s charity made a seeping feeling of shame crawl over them.

“Correct. Do you promise to abide by my condition?”

“...Y-Yes. We swear it. I will do everything I can to return this debt one day, so please take us into your care. Thank you very much,” Miharu said with a pained expression, bowing her head low before Rio.

“P-Please.” Beside her, Aki and Masato followed her lead and lowered their heads, too.

Rio shook his head. “Then, it’s been decided. Please raise your heads. I’m sure we must all be getting hungry by now, right? Let’s leave the details for later and have some food first. I’ll prepare it now — does anyone have any requests?” he said brightly, wanting to move beyond the heavy atmosphere.

“U-Umm, I can help! I know the favorites of the other two, and I’m pretty good at cooking, so I’d like you to leave the cooking to me from here on out!” Miharu offered without missing a beat.

“Then, could you please?” Rio asked hesitantly.

“Yes, I’ll do my best!” Miharu clenched both her fists, fired up with motivation.

“Ah, then I’ll help, too!” Aki offered in a fluster.

Masato interrupted her. “S-Stop it, Aki. Didn’t you turn the hamburg steak last time into ash?”

“S-Shut up! That was just a coincidence. And anyway, brother said it was delicious,” Aki objected with a sullen pout.

“Yeah, no. No way that wasn’t just flattery — bro was just being polite,” Masato stated firmly with a grimace.

The fact that Miharu wasn’t particularly jumping to Aki’s defense showed that Aki’s cooking really was terrible.

“Miharu and I can handle cooking for four people between the two of us, I think. I’ll need to explain how to use the kitchen, too, so the two of you can go take a bath in the meantime,” Rio suggested, hoping to appease the two that were noisily bickering away at each other.

“This house even has a bath?” Aki’s eyes widened, impressed. She had been prepared to camp outside just a short while ago, so hearing that there was a bath made a young girl her age extremely elated.

“First, you use the magic tool... the artifact, it’s called. I’ll have to explain how to use the one in the bathroom first, so follow me, everyone.” Thus, the party made their way to the bathroom.

“Here we are.” Rio opened the door that led from the changing area into the bathing area and invited Miharu, Aki, and Masato inside.

“Excuse me,” they said, hesitantly entering the bathroom.

“Wow...” Aki murmured in surprise and astonishment without thinking at the peculiar facilities.

Rio’s playful spirit as a former Japanese person caused him to choose a warm brick at the door of the changing room, giving the illusion of a hot springs entrance. The actual interior of the bathroom was installed in what undeniably mimicked the design of a hot springs.

The changing room was spacious, but the bathroom was even more so; over half the room was occupied by a washing space made of tiled stone, while the remaining area was utilized by a splendid stone bathtub that could easily fit several adults in the water at the same time.

Magical spouts that constantly supplied fresh bath water were set along the stone surface. Thanks to the magic artifacts in the middle of the stone bath, other than regular maintenance, there was no need to change the water or frequently clean the space.

The water in the stone bath was clear, and a white steam was dancing off its surface.

“You can touch the round stones set in the washing area when you’re washing your hair and body. It’ll absorb essence proportionate to how long you touch it, then produce water from that spout. The right stone is for the higher spout, and the left stone is for the lower spout.”

Rio approached the wall of the washing area and showed them the artifacts as he spoke. At a glance, the amount of essence flowing from the three of them was fairly substantial, so they wouldn’t have had a problem using it.

“C-Can I touch it?” Masato asked, brimming with curiosity.

“Sure. The water comes out pretty fast, so be careful.”

With Rio’s permission, Masato triumphantly reached for the round stone on the left with the formula carved. The lower water spout immediately started bubbling forth with water.

“Wow! That’s amazing!” Masato exclaimed, bursting with pure excitement.

“There are four types of soap in those metal containers over there. Starting from the right, there’s shampoo, conditioner, face wash, and body wash. The towels are on the shelf in the changing room — feel free to take one each.”

“O-Okay.” Miharu and Aki nodded timidly. They couldn’t help but feel bewildered at how substantial the bathing facilities were.

“So, that’s how you use the bath. Who wants to get in first?” Rio asked. Aki and Masato looked at each other.

“I’m going first!”

“I wanna go first!”

Their words effortlessly overlapped with each other’s.

◇◇◇

After an intense round of rock-paper-scissors, it was decided that Aki would bathe first. Masato agreed to explore the rest of the house in order to relieve his boredom. In the meantime, Rio and Miharu would work together to prepare dinner for everyone.

Miharu put on an apron that she borrowed from Rio over the top of her uniform, making her look very domestic and cute. Rio became nervous, which was something out of character for him.

“Okay, shall we start cooking?” he said with an uncomfortable smile. He had already explained where the cookware was placed, where the seasoning was stored, the ingredients in the refrigerator, and how to use the artifacts for fire and water. They had also decided on a Japanese menu.

“Yes. I’ll make the miso soup and chopped burdock root, as well as the steamed dish.” Miharu nodded with a carefree smile as she began to prepare the miso soup first. Her movements showed no sign of hesitation, making it clear that she was used to cooking.

...She really is good at cooking.

As Rio prepared to boil the rice, he admired Miharu’s movements, even captivated by them. Before him was a Miharu that he didn’t know. It was refreshing.

“U-Umm, is there something wrong with how I’m cooking?” Miharu asked hesitantly, noticing Rio’s gaze.

Rio flinched. “N-No, I’m sorry. I was just impressed with how well you cook,” he replied awkwardly.

“Ahaha, thank you very much. It’s all thanks to my mother. She taught me how to cook a lot of things when I was little.” Miharu grinned with embarrassment, but never stopped moving her busy hands.

“Your mother... I see.”

Rio — no, Amakawa Haruto within Rio — had no idea that Miharu learned to cook from her mother. She probably began learning after she became distanced from Haruto.

Chapter 8: Operating in the Shadows

Two weeks after Rio departed from the spirit folk village...

Left behind in the Strahl region, Miharu and the others lived a completely peaceful life, leisurely waiting for Rio’s return. Presently, they were in the middle of a break from their language studies. Aishia and Masato were both taking a nap, while Miharu and Aki sat on the living room sofa sipping tea.

“I wonder if Haruto will be back soon...?” Miharu mumbled to herself. While her words were formed as a question, she was more or less speaking to herself. Nonetheless, her mumbling still clearly reached Aki’s ears.

“Miharu, you’ve been saying the same thing for a few days now,” she said with a strained laugh.

For some reason, Miharu flinched. “Eh...? R-Really?” she asked in a high-pitched voice, inclining her head.

Miharu wasn’t quite sure why she flinched, but now that Aki had mentioned it, she had been finding herself thinking about Haruto out of the blue these days.

“...What’s wrong, Miharu?” Aki picked up on the delicate change in Miharu and watched her doubtfully.

“Nothing at all. Why?” Miharu put on a calm air and met Aki’s gaze. Aki didn’t seem entirely convinced, but changed the subject anyway. “It’s nothing... But I do wonder how long we’re going to live like this, yeah?”

“Umm, what do you mean by ‘like this’?” Miharu asked.

“We should have been middle school and high school students, you know? Masato only just reached the sixth grade, and our new school lives were meant to start... But now Takahisa and Satsuki are both gone, and we may never meet Mom and the others ever again. I don’t really know, but the longer this life continues, the more I feel like we won’t be able to go back anymore.” Aki’s expression fell helplessly.

“So you’re worried...” Miharu slowly stood up and moved next to Aki, stroking her back. Aki leaned into her to be doted upon.

“...Aren’t you worried, Miharu?” she asked nervously.

“I am... a little uneasy, but probably not as much as you.” Miharu shook her head with a faint smile.

Aki looked up at Miharu’s face curiously. “Why?”

“I have you and Masato with me, as well as Ai-chan and Haruto. I feel safe. That’s why I’m wondering if there’s anything I could do in return, because I feel sorry that you’re worried,” Miharu answered. Her smile was bittersweet this time.

“...You’re strong, Miharu.”

“I’m weak. If I didn’t have you and the others, I wouldn’t be alive right now.”

“I don’t believe that... If anything, I should be saying that. I don’t know where I’d be right now if I didn’t have you with me.”

“Hehe, thank you.”

“Yeah...” Aki said shyly, still seeming to be a little unsure.

“Aki. Thanks to Haruto, we’ve been able to live so peacefully. I think that’s an amazing blessing, don’t you? So... how about you try to think a little more positively?” Miharu asked gently, trying to persuade Aki.

“That’s... Yeah. I think so too, but...”

“I guess you still want to return to Earth, right?”

“Yeah... Don’t you want to go back, Miharu?”

“If I said I didn’t want to go home... that would probably be a lie, but I don’t think there’s any need to hurry. Haruto’s willing to help us out, after all.”

“Haruto...” Aki murmured Haruto’s name, her expression turning gloomy. She was much better about it now, but she still couldn’t help but think of someone in the back of her mind whenever she heard the name. In particular, when it was coming from Miharu’s mouth, it sometimes left her feeling quite conflicted.

“What do you think of Haruto?” Aki suddenly asked Miharu. She had noticed that Miharu’s mind had been on Haruto lately, so she was curious.

“Hm? Umm... What do you mean by that?” Miharu asked in return, watching Aki’s expression with uncertainty.

“Nothing, really... It’s just — even though you’re normally bad around boys, you seem to act really natural when you’re around Haruto... Being totally in sync when you’re cooking together and laughing with each other. That’s why I was just wondering... So, how do you feel about him?” Aki explained her question hesitantly, but directly, so that Miharu couldn’t avoid answering her.

“H-How, I wonder? He’s reliable, and a really nice person, I think. And...” Miharu replied timidly, searching within herself with a contemplative expression.

“...And?” Aki pressed.

“I don’t know if it’s because his name is the same, but he kind of reminds me of Haru-kun... I guess? Maybe?”

“W-What are you saying?! Miharu!” Aki’s expression changed with a gasp, her tone of voice immediately turning rougher.

“...Huh? Ah! S-Sorry! That wasn’t my intention!” Miharu belatedly processed what she had said out loud and shook her head in a fluster. While she had always made sure not to mention Haruto in front of Aki, thinking about the Haruto in this world made his name unintentionally slip out of her mouth.

“Hey, Miharu... Do you really still remember him? Even though you might never see him again? He probably doesn’t remember you anymore, either, so don’t confuse him with this Haruto. That would be rude,” Aki snapped. She was filled with regret as soon as she finished speaking, because she had been the one overlapping this Haruto and Amakawa Haruto in her thoughts.

“...I’m sorry — I got too heated up about it. I’m going to go clear my head.”

Aki stood up and went out the front door for some fresh air, her words filled with guilt.

◇◇◇

I’m such a fool...

As soon as Aki stepped through the door, she immediately crouched down outside the house in shame. She didn’t want to be inside; despite being told not to leave the house for any reason, she wanted some fresh air.

I don’t have any right to blame Miharu... Aki regretted bitterly, heaving a deep sigh. Even Miharu, who was typically of a warm disposition, might have become angry with her this time around.

Maybe Miharu still likes him after all? Then... should I apologize for saying such terrible things? But... A complicated emotion filled Aki — she wanted to apologize to Miharu and go back to the way things were, but whenever Amakawa Haruto’s name came up, she couldn’t help but recall everything about him.

“Argh, enough!” Aki yelled loudly after some time had passed, her head filled with too many thoughts to process.

“Uurgh...” A small groan sounded from a short distance away, but it was too soft to reach Aki’s ears. The front door of the house opened and Miharu’s hesitant figure appeared.

“U-Umm, you know, Aki. ...Huh? Kya!” She tried to shyly call out to Aki, but spotted two gray creatures instead. They were shaped like humans but clearly not human, and they sauntered about the forest roughly 20 meters away from the house. Miharu couldn’t hold back her scream.

“W-What’s wrong, Miharu? Eek! W-What is that?!” Aki had flinched in surprise at Miharu’s scream, then followed her gaze; she recoiled in horror at the sight of the monstrous creatures.

Miharu snapped out of her fear with a gasp. “A-Aki, hurry inside the house! Now!” she called out in a fluster.

“B-But it’s weird... Shouldn’t there be a barrier keeping them out?” Aki observed the movements of the creatures carefully — it didn’t seem like they had noticed her.

“No! Hurry and get Ai-chan, quickly,” Miharu said fretfully, when Aishia materialized right beside her.

“It’s okay... I’m already here.” She had a somewhat sleepy expression and seemed to have just woken up.

Miharu let out a sigh of relief. “Ah, Ai-chan...”

“Aishia... W-What is that?” Aki asked her timidly.

“Monsters, probably. They can’t enter the barrier, but they may be drawn to the essence of the barrier itself. I’ll take care of this quickly — you two get inside,” Aishia instructed Miharu and Aki as she vigilantly stared at the strange creatures.

Understanding they would be nothing but a hindrance, Miharu quickly ran over to Aki. “O-Okay. Let’s go, Aki.”

She pulled her by the hand toward the house. Once Aishia confirmed that they had left, she slowly started to walk forward.

“They’re person-shaped, but don’t seem to be human...?” Seeing the strange monsters gave her an eerie feeling, making her incline her head.

Their eyes were filled with madness, but other than their skin tones, they looked just like humans. That much was clear now that Aishia was closer to them... Though once she readjusted her thinking, the truth was that none of that mattered.

I’ll find out if I defeat them... I must protect the others in this house. That was the role Haruto had given her.

With that in mind, Aishia held her right hand out toward the monsters. The faint light indicative of spirit arts started to flow from her hand as a sign of her refined ode manipulation.

Aishia fired a shock wave bullet at the monster — the invisible attack made direct contact, and a sound reminiscent of the impact of a hammer echoed as the monster’s body was sent flying through the air. Boom!

The force was enough to turn a human’s bones to dust.

Aishia adjusted her sights onto the remaining monster mercilessly.

“Uuuuuargh!”

Just then, another one leaped out of the forest. It was similar to the other two in terms of its humanoid shape, but its skin was darker. For some reason, the darker monster was able to easily slip through the barrier and rush straight for Miharu and Aki, who had retreated to the front door. It moved fairly quickly.

“Aki, get down!”

Miharu saw the black monster closing in on them and, as a last minute resort, used her own body as a shield to cover Aki, hugging her close.

“Eh?!” Aki was thrown off balance at the sudden movement, unsure of what was happening, though she could immediately tell that Miharu was covering her by holding herself close. Once she noticed the black monster approaching them, she understood why Miharu had done such a thing.

“M-Miharu?!” Aki couldn’t help but yell. Miharu was in danger — it was evident there was nothing they could do, but Aki struggled and squirmed anyway.

Meanwhile, Aishia had reacted by aiming her right hand at the black monster, but she soon lowered it. The monster’s death was certain, even without her lifting a hand.

There were several meters left until the black monster would reach Miharu and Aki, when a black shadow descended from the skies gracefully. Held in Miharu’s embrace, Aki was able to see the figure from behind.

She immediately knew who it was.

Reflected in her eyes and dressed in the armor of the Black Wyvern was Rio’s familiar figure.

“Aaugh?!” The black monster seemed to be taken aback at how Rio suddenly appeared before its eyes. Its speed fell for a moment, freezing on the spot — which proved to be a fatal mistake.

Rio immediately aimed for the opening the monster had created. He sprung forward with all his might and thrust the hilt of his sword with pinpoint accuracy into the solar plexus of the monster, blowing it back ten meters. A real human would have been wracked with unbearable pain and struggled for breath. If anything, the purely physical damage of the attack would have left them with ruptured organs.

“Come again soon. I’ll welcome gatherings like today at any time,” Dryas said with a pleasant expression as she saw Rio and the others off.

“Yes, we’ll bring lots of snacks again.” Rio bowed with a gentle smile.

“I’m counting on you to bring more manju. Ah, and please teach Orphia and the others how to make it as well, for when you’ve left on your journey.” It seemed like Dryas had completely fallen for the charms of the manju.

“Sure thing,” Rio agreed cheerfully, making Sara and the others laugh happily in anticipation.

“All right — take care, then. Did you make sure you didn’t forget anything?” Dryas asked.

“Yes,” Rio and the others nodded in unison. Or so they thought —

“Ah, I forgot to invite Arslan to come along, too!” Vera said.

“Ahaha... Come to think of it, you said you’d bring him along before you came to our house. I thought he was busy since he didn’t show up...” Latifa said with a strained smile.

“Ack! I-I got so excited that I forgot. I have to hurry back and apologize!” Vera said with a regretful look.

After that, they all visited Arslan’s house and went through quite a bit to cheer him up from his grumpy mood.

◇◇◇

After that, days in the village passed by in a flash.

Every day was filled with laughter: Rio participated in the tea parties hosted by Orphia, sparred with Sara, Uzuma and the other village warriors, drank with Alma and Dominic, played with Latifa, Vera, Arslan, and the other village kids, and taught the village ladies how to cook the recipes from Yagumo.

Furthermore, while Rio was fully enjoying his life in the village, construction of his house was progressing smoothly under Dominic’s leadership. On a day two weeks after he had returned to the village, Rio paid a visit to the construction site, where huge numbers of dwarves were busily laboring away. When Dominic spotted Rio, he paused in his supervising and approached Rio with a grin.

“Yo, Rio. You’re here.”

“Good day, Dominic. I’m sorry for leaving everything to you...” Rio bowed his head in gratitude.

“Don’t worry about it — I was the one who wanted to build it. You’re not staying in the village for long, so spend as much time with Alma and the others as you can,” Dominic said, smacking Rio’s arm heartily.

“Truly, thank you very much. Speaking of which, the house is looking far more extravagant than I imagined,” Rio said with a faintly apologetic smile, looking around at the construction scene before him, where a huge rock stood that completely occupied the plot, which easily surpassed 200 square meters.

“Hahaha, I know, right?” Dominic agreed with a lively laugh.

“I heard you were processing natural rock to make the house, but are you hollowing it out?”

“Yeah, with spirit arts. It’s pretty big — we’ve extended part of it with space spirit arts, and we’ll make a second floor, too, so there’ll be lots of rooms.”

Rio’s smile twitched at the unexpectedly large scale. “Ahaha... That’s too much for one person to live alone.”

“Well, you’ll have a household yourself one day, so I figured I’d make it big enough for that. Although, it wouldn’t be enough if you were to take several wives and have children like me...” Dominic said while nodding.

The spirit folk village allowed one husband to take many wives, or even the opposite; Dominic himself had four wives. Because of that experience, Dominic would recommend polygamy to Rio at every possible chance.

“No, well, you never know what the future holds, or something, ahaha...” Rio personally had no intention of becoming a polygamist — he didn’t even have any desire for marriage — so he could only offer a reserved response with a forced smile.

W-Well, I guess it’ll be easier to live in, so it shouldn’t be a problem... I think. While the size is a little unexpected, it seems like it’s being built exactly as I requested, so I guess they can do what they want, Rio thought in resignation.

The conditions Rio had requested beforehand were for it to blend smoothly with the environment when camping, and that the house was sturdy enough to prevent outside intruders from breaking in. By making the house from a boulder, both of those requests were fulfilled perfectly. With this, he would be able to set a base for his activities outside of the cities when he moved through Strahl.

And so, the two of them continued talking, until —

“Hey, Head Elder Dominic! Do you have a moment?” one of the dwarves on location called.

“Oh, it looks like I’m being summoned. Well, just leave the construction to me, and look forward to its completion. I’ll call you immediately when it’s done. We can raise a glass in celebration!” Dominic said with a smile, before leaving Rio behind to head for the work site.

“...Looks like I owe the villagers again,” Rio muttered, troubled, as he watched the dwarves happily working away.

◇◇◇

Less than a month later, Rio’s house made of rock was complete.

The appearance of the home was truly rustic — in fact, apart from the entrance and several small ventilation windows, it looked just like a regular old boulder.

However, in complete contrast to the exterior, the interior was a wide and comfortable living space with custom-made furniture and all kinds of sorcery woven into its luxurious facilities. It went without saying that a wild housewarming party was held upon its completion, filled with singing and drinks. Furthermore, when Rio immediately moved in upon its completion to test the facilities, it was decided that — naturally — Latifa would live with him too.

After a while, Vera and Arslan also came to sleep over, then Sara and the others were invited partly as their guardians. And so, their lively days continued.

Thus, as winter approached, the new year arrived — year 1000 of the Holy Era. On a day when Rio’s departure for the Strahl region was steadily approaching and he was in the bathtub of his stone house...

The interior of the spacious bathing area was purposefully carved into bare stone, making a rocky bath that allowed for an experience similar to an outdoor hot spring. Rio washed his hair, face and body, before finally sinking into the water.

“...Hah.”

With a sigh, his fatigue from the day melted away.

Tomorrow’s the day, finally, he thought, gazing up at the rock ceiling that was intentionally left bare.

It was so comfortable, he almost wanted to extend his stay, but he didn’t want to pamper himself here.

He couldn’t afford to stand still.

There was no doubt that unwanted memories from his past would resurface once he returned to Strahl; it was possible he couldn’t remain the same person he had been until now.

Even so, he chose to move forward — that was what he had decided when he left the Yagumo region. That was why he had to move forward... Even if he reached the point of no return.

With a deep breath, Rio reaffirmed his resolve.

“Onii-chan, may I come in?” a cute voice said from the doorway to the bathroom.

“Yeah... Huh?”

Rio nodded reflexively, before he realized something was strange, and looked up at the source of the voice. Latifa, who had been sticking her head out of the changing room area, heard Rio’s reply and stepped into the bathroom hesitantly, clad in nothing but a single bath towel.

“Ehehe.” Latifa grinned shyly.

“...” Unable to close his open mouth, Rio simply stared at her in shock.

Her pale orange hair was tied back to reveal her nape, the towel emphasizing her small and modest chest. Her waist and hips were slender, yet well-balanced, and her legs were lean and white — despite being only thirteen, Latifa was already starting to show her womanly charms.

“O-Onii-chan, it’s embarrassing when you stare at me like that,” Latifa said, fidgeting. With that, Rio snapped back to his senses.

“S-Sorry. Wait, why are you here?!” Rio asked while averting his gaze from Latifa’s body in a panic.

“Umm. I wanted to wash Onii-chan’s back. May I?” Latifa smiled with a bashful yet pleased grin, noticing that Rio was seeing her as a member of the opposite sex and not just a little sister.

“No, of course not. You need to leave immediately,” Rio said with a high-pitched voice.

“I-It’s okay. I-I’m wearing a bath towel, so don’t worry. Not to mention the fact that you’ll be leaving the village tomorrow. So, let me have this just for today?”

“N-No, but...”

“Just for today, please!” Latifa hung onto him insistently when he expressed his reluctance. Since she was leaning into the bathtub from outside of it, the placement of her chest was rather precarious, making Rio beside himself with worry.

“N-No means no. Come on, put on your clothes or you’ll catch a cold. Okay?” Rio replied with his eyes averted, unable to find a good way to reject her.

“Hmph, then I’ll just get into the bath with Onii-chan like this. You sure?” Latifa puffed up her cheeks cutely, resisting to the bitter end.

Now that she had gathered up enough courage to come this far, she wasn’t going to back down without a fight. Despite her face being flushed with embarrassment, she tried to remove her bath towel with a trembling hand.

“A-All right! All right, I got it! Calm down, Latifa. You can wash me,” Rio said in a panic as he caught a glimpse of Latifa’s naked body from the corner of his eye. Latifa’s expression lit up; she was beaming.

“R-Really?!”

“...Yeah, just for today,” Rio gave in, nodding.

“Yup! Okay, come over here!” Latifa said, immediately hurrying toward the washing area.

“All right, I’m getting out now.”

“Okay.”

Rio checked that Latifa had looked away, before standing up from the bathtub and swiftly wrapping a towel around his waist. He then walked over to her and sat down on the bath stool in front of her.

“Ehehe.” Latifa’s cheeks warmed happily.

I mean... It’s just a back wash... Rio smiled in amusement.

“Okay, I’m gonna wash you now. Erm, let me know if I miss any spots.”

“Yeah, sure.”

Latifa rubbed the soap against a towel to lather it, then began to awkwardly wash Rio’s back. She seemed to be feeling nervous now that she was in the middle of doing it, moving timidly despite her earlier courage. Silently, she rubbed away with her hands, gradually falling into a calm state of mind.

Meanwhile, Rio was still feeling confused, but had regained most of his composure. He couldn’t find the words to start a conversation, but he smiled happily at the feeling of Latifa’s hands as she was doing her best.

“Latifa, that’s enough. Thank you,” Rio thanked her after a while, his voice soft.

“O-Okay. I’ll pour the water, then.”

Splash. Latifa touched the round stone artifact that supplied hot water and filled a tub with water to pour over Rio’s back. After repeating that a few times —

“...Onii-chan’s back is really big after all,” she murmured quietly.

“Really?”

“Yeah... I wonder if it’ll be bigger the next time we meet?”

“Who knows? I think I’ll stop growing soon, but — wait, L-Latifa?!”

Rio was replying with a strained smile when, suddenly, he could feel a soft sensation against his back. He flinched.

Latifa had suddenly hugged Rio from behind, drawing close enough to rub their cheeks together before he had realized it.

“...What’s wrong all of a sudden?” Rio asked, hiding his uneasiness. He could feel Latifa’s body heat through her towel; the areas where their skin touching directly was burning hot.

“Hey, Onii-chan... You’ll come back to the village again this time, right?” Latifa asked worriedly.

“...Latifa?” Rio called, checking on her.

“You’ll come back, right?” Latifa repeated the same question insistently.

Rio felt as though she had seen right through him. He guiltily averted his eyes, bit down on his lip and closed his eyes, then searched inside himself.

“...If you’re waiting for me, I’ll return,” he answered slowly.

“No — you have to come back,” Latifa demanded as she pouted with a sulk.

“...I see. I’ll have to come back, then.”

Rio forced down the shameful feelings that he had, and spoke with an apologetic, strained smile. Latifa’s expression brightened a little.

“Yup. Make sure you come back earlier this time. Please?”

“Yeah. I promised, after all. I’ll come back when I can find the time,” Rio nodded with a smile.

He felt guilty because of his own reluctance; he wondered if it was really okay for him to have a place to return to when he was setting off on the path of revenge.

However, his desire to return to the village was his pure, honest feelings. And with that, he would return as long as Latifa wanted him to, he decided.

“...By the way, Latifa. You’ll catch a cold like that, so let’s get in the bath,” Rio suggested with a bitter smile to Latifa, who was still hanging onto him.

“Huh...? Ah, okay! That’s right, ehehe.”

Latifa distanced herself from Rio in a hurry, grinning bashfully.

◇◇◇

The next morning, Rio made his way to the village square, which was where he was to depart from.

The usual faces were there to see him off, along with the village’s elders. After Rio finished saying his goodbyes to Sara and the others, the three head elders approached him last.

“Lord Rio, take this with you,” Ursula said, handing Rio a sparkling, jade-colored spirit stone the size of a fist.

“...Is this spirit stone some kind of magical artifact? Is there some kind of formula sealed in it?” Rio asked, his gaze absorbed by the spirit stone in his hand.

A spirit stone could be used as a magic artifact by having a spell formula sealed within, but it would just look like a spirit stone to those who didn’t have the eye to see essence. The formula within was being reflected in Rio’s eyes.

“This is a teleport crystal — an artifact filled with sorcery that moves the user to a predetermined destination. The activation chant to use it is Transilio. I’ve already put the coordinates in, so you can return to the village easily with this. But it’s a one way method of travel, so you won’t be able to return to your starting position,” Ursula explained; the sorcery activation, however, required more than just chanting the keyword in order to prevent an accident from occurring.

“An item like this... Did you recently make it just for me?”

“Indeed. There used to be several of them in the village in the past, but they became unnecessary over our long history. The spirit stones had their formulas removed and were repurposed as other magic artifacts. After all, no one ever leaves the village. But, since you leave the village rather frequently, we figured it would be more convenient for you to have.”

“But the spirit stone is such a high quality. It’s sizable, too. Isn’t it a valuable item?” Rio questioned at Ursula’s generous words.

While a spirit stone could be turned into an artifact with sorcery, it also had a wide range of other uses, such as being a pure energy source for other artifacts, or for storing magic essence to use in case of emergencies. The essence capacity that could be stored varied depending on the quality of the stone, and the color of the stone changed based on the amount of essence stored. Among them, stones that could turn emerald green were said to be of high quality — proof it could store a vast amount of essence.

Logically, the bigger the stone, the more essence could be stored. However, because of the difference in stone quality, that reasoning could differ, too.

“It’s nothing; we’ve been making spirit stones for years and years now, so we have plenty of good stones in stock. There’s no need for you to worry.” Ursula shook her head with a smile.

“But even so, I’ve received so many items already... I couldn’t possibly accept any more than what I have. I’ve just returned and had a house built for me, and there was the equipment set and the Time-Space Cache from last time. I’ve received so many other good quality spirit stones, too.” Rio’s expression clouded apologetically.

“Don’t worry about it. Like we said last time, you are our sworn friend. It would be a dishonor to us spirit folk for our sworn friend to depart on a journey empty-handed, so just accept it. Well... it was Syldora and Ursula who made it, actually.” Dominic laughed merrily, looking over at the two of them.

“We simply used a spare spirit stone — the only thing it took was time. Space sorcery has complicated formulas, so it took some effort to get the coordinates right, but it was no big deal.” Syldora shook his head, smiling in faint embarrassment.

“Hohoho, Latifa was lonely while Lord Rio was in Yagumo. Hopefully this will help you return faster this time. We’ll need to discuss further, but it may be a good idea to use that to bring Latifa and Lord Rio’s cousin together for a meeting someday.” Ursula opened her mouth to deal the finishing blow.

“...Thank you very much, truly. For all the things you’ve done for me.” Rio bowed his head deeply.

“Well, that’s that. Those girls over there would be happier to have you around, kid. Come back a bit more often.” Dominic looked over to Sara, Orphia, and Alma with a grin.

“Head Elder!”

“Grandfather!”

Sara and Alma blushed furiously and yelled in shock. Meanwhile, Orphia was avoiding digging her own grave by smiling cheerfully.

“Ooh, scary, scary.” Dominic shuddered exaggeratedly and quickly made his exit.

Then, Latifa approached Rio with springy footsteps.

“Have a good trip, Onii-chan,” she said, hugging Rio.

“Yeah, I’ll be back soon.” Rio smiled gently and petted Latifa’s head.

“Do you cook often, Haruto?” Miharu asked.

“Yes, I do. I’m traveling alone, so it’s a bit of a hobby for me.” Rio shrugged his shoulders, Miharu smiled with some embarrassment.

“I’ve actually never eaten a man’s cooking before, so I’m looking forward to it.”

“...I don’t think you’ll find anything different about my cooking, but I’ll do my best.”

Rio was a little — no, a lot more motivated than usual, but he couldn’t stay elated forever, so he reigned in his emotions.

After that, the two of them worked together in a strangely harmonious way, synchronizing with each other efficiently as they cooked. They both praised each other’s skills and responded humbly, taste-testing and exchanging opinions, and overall spending a peaceful time together.

◇◇◇

Just as Rio and Miharu were starting to cook, Aki was sinking into the water of the stone bath; looking up at the ceiling in a daze, she thought back on the various events that occurred today.

So many surprising things happened. They came to a world that wasn’t Earth, found themselves in a disastrous situation, finally stumbled upon some strangers — only to be unable to communicate with them — and were nearly made into slaves. However, they were immediately saved by another stranger, who agreed to shelter them and thus resulted in her leisurely relaxing in a bathtub.

We really are so indebted to Haruto... Haruto... Haruto...

In the back of Aki’s mind, Haruto... Rio’s face came to mind, eventually morphing into the painful memories of someone else, and her expression changed to one that was bitter and sour.

Hmph... Haruto’s different from that guy, but he keeps coming to mind anyway.

“He” was Amakawa Haruto — the person who had been Aki’s older brother.

Aki hated him — not for a logical reason, but an emotional one. Haruto and their father had chosen to abandon Aki and their mother, and Haruto was a liar that didn’t keep his promises.

However, Aki loved her mother from the bottom of her heart, as her mother had raised her with great care. After the divorce, her mother should have been rife with pain, yet she showed no weakness in front of Aki and selflessly poured all her love into her daughter.

Aki’s parents had divorced when she was still four years old, so she only had vague memories of those times, but she remembered living quite happily until the divorce. Now that she was looking back on it, Aki could admit it: she had really loved her family back then.

In particular, she had loved her older brother, and was extremely attached to him. She was just as attached to Miharu, the older girl living in the house next door.

Back then, both of their parents in the Amakawa house worked full time, so they were often left in the care of Miharu’s family. Aki was constantly looked after by Haruto and Miharu. She was always by their side, which was why she knew better than anyone that Haruto and Miharu were very close, and really suited each other, in her opinion.

At the time, the two were so close that they often created spaces where they were the only two that existed. For Aki, however, they were her ideal older brother and sister. When the two of them were happy, Aki was happy, too. What made her the happiest of all was when the two of them doted on her.

Being spoiled by Haruto and Miharu had been a special privilege limited to only Aki, and she was the only one unconditionally permitted into the unique space the two of them made for each other.

Aki was the only one who was treated specially by the two of them, making her feel special in turn. It made her truly happy.

And so, Aki had begged Haruto and Miharu, that the three of them would always stay together, and the two of them swore to keep Aki by their sides even when they grew up. Haruto promised to not only protect Miharu, but Aki, too. Despite this, it was like he had changed his mind when Haruto left with the man who had once been Aki’s father.

“Liar,” Aki murmured involuntarily, echoing with the sound of the water bubbling from the spout.

The only one who kept their promise and kept Aki close to her was her beloved Miharu. She continued to treat Aki as her own precious little sister, even now.

Forget it... Who cares about that guy. I haven’t thought about him in so long... Aki’s face twisted horribly at the indescribable and complicated feelings within her. She shook her head.

Until now, there had been no mention of Haruto in her house, so Aki had never expressed her hatred for Haruto in front of her family before. The stepfather her mother remarried aside, her older stepbrother Takahisa and younger stepbrother Masato probably didn’t even know Haruto’s name.

However, there was one person who knew of the hatred Aki held toward Haruto — Miharu. Once, Aki had shown great anger in front of Miharu in saying that she didn’t care about someone like Haruto.

Aki knew her mother had raised her singlehandedly, that her mother was secretly in so much pain about Haruto and her father, so much so that her mother cried alone late at night... Because of those things, Aki couldn’t forgive them. Before she knew it, she detested them.

That was why it happened, all those years ago...

One day, Miharu had mentioned Haruto while reminiscing about something, and Aki had reacted with rejection. At the time, Miharu had apologized with sadness.

“I’m sorry,” she had said. Ever since then, Miharu never brought up Haruto before Aki ever again.

Today, upon hearing Haruto’s name, she had involuntarily thought of their Haruto. When Aki had accidentally showed an odd attitude in front of Haruto and the others, Miharu had called Aki’s name as though she had seen right through her.

Ever since Aki let her anger toward Haruto be known, Miharu had continued to treat her like a little sister. However, Aki wondered what kind of feelings she had right now.

Aah, geez! I don’t even want to think about him!

The more she wanted to erase her past, the harder it was to stop the memories from flowing out once she remembered something. Splash! Aki writhed about the bathtub in shame.

Let’s think about something else. That’s right... Onii-chan. I should think about Onii-chan. Satsuki, too.

Aki decided to think about the older brother that wasn’t Amakawa Haruto — Sendo Takahisa, as well as the upperclassman of Miharu and Takahisa, Sumeragi Satsuki.

Sendo Takahisa was a child from Aki’s stepfather’s previous marriage, and Masato’s older brother. He was turning sixteen years old this year — the same age as Miharu. Through Aki’s connection, he was introduced to Miharu and fell in love with her at first sight, and had felt strongly for her ever since. He could be a bit unreliable at times, but he was sociable and kind, accomplished in both his studies and sports, and handsome enough to be quite popular with the girls. Only a few years had passed since her mother remarried, but Aki was already proud to call him her brother.

Sumeragi Satsuki was an upperclassman from Miharu and Takahisa’s middle school days, and was the president of the student council they were a part of. Miharu and Takahisa had just entered high school and reunited with Satsuki at the opening ceremony before coming to this world, but Aki was acquainted with her, too.

Satsuki was the charismatic daughter of a famous company’s president. Aki secretly admired her, seeing her as a perfect superhuman with no weaknesses at all.

“Onii-chan, Satsuki... I hope the two of them are all right,” Aki muttered worriedly.

The two of them were far more reliable than herself and Masato, but when she looked back upon the events that she experienced since coming to this world, she couldn’t help but feel excessively anxious. Especially when she considered the parts where her brother Takahisa was lacking.

When she thought about it calmly, it was possible they had run into a similar situation to hers. As worst case scenarios flashed through the back of her mind, uneasiness endlessly surged within her.

Nevertheless, there was nothing she could do about it. She wouldn’t even be able to live in this world if it weren’t for Haruto, so she couldn’t pointlessly make a fuss over it for nothing. Aki had enough foresight to know that much.

“All I can do now is learn as much as I can so that I can adjust to this world as quickly as possible. Then, we’ll all go home together, to where Mom and Dad are, on Earth.” Aki might’ve been averting her eyes from the reality of the situation, but it was better than running away from it; this was what she told herself. She hadn’t given up hope, at least.

...I wonder if Haruto’s ever thought about returning to Earth. He said he was a university student in his previous life... Is that the thing they call “rebirth”? I guess such a thing actually exists...

She began thinking about the guardian who would have to look out for her in the near future. There was something fleeting about him, and he had many unknown sides of himself that were surrounded in mystery, but she definitely didn’t think he was a bad person. If anything, he was too good of a person.

His personality was calm and polite, his face was pretty and well-refined, and he was very reliable; she couldn’t see any faults in him so far.

Ah... I should get up soon.

Aki’s head began to spin as she realized she was suddenly getting dizzy. While it was partly because she had stayed in the water for too long because it felt so good, the fact she had been thinking so hard played a large part in it as well.

She stood up slowly and placed a hand against the stone surface as she supported her staggering body. Once her dizziness waned, Aki slowly headed toward the changing room, where the cool air inside felt good.

She was extremely reluctant to wear the same pair of underwear twice, but she unfortunately didn’t have a change of underwear, so she endured it and put on a childish pair of shorts. She didn’t have a bra for reasons related to her growth, so she wore a camisole that was just as childish as her shorts.

“Hmph... I wish I was a little more like Miharu,” Aki muttered to herself as she touched her flat body; she was at the age where she admired Miharu for her slender but feminine frame.

Once she finished changing, she returned to the living room. A delicious-smelling scent was wafting throughout, and when she fearfully peered into the kitchen, she found Rio and Miharu intimately making dinner together.

“...” Aki tried to call out to the two of them, but for some reason, her words wouldn’t come out. She felt a strange sense of déjà vu as she watched the two of them in a daze, but she shook her head from left to right and brushed it off.

“You’re done, Aki? Were you able to unwind a little?” Rio noticed Aki and called out to her in a friendly voice.

“Ah, yes. It was a very nice bath. Thank you for letting me use it first.” Aki bowed her head hesitantly.

“I’m glad to hear that. Can you go tell Masato that it’s his turn to get in? He’s probably off exploring some part of the house.”

“E-Exploring... I understand.” Aki nodded in exasperation at Masato’s childishness.

“Also, there are cold drinks in that box over there that you can take as you wish. The glasses are in that shelf over there, so help yourself to whatever you want.”

“T-Thank you very much. You’re so considerate of everything...” Aki bowed her head — Rio really left nothing to be desired.

Afterward, Aki found Masato and told him to go take a bath, then sat down on the sofa in the living room to drink her iced tea.

It sure smells nice.

As she enjoyed the tropical scent of the iced tea and cool sensation of the metal mug, Aki absentmindedly watched what was going on in the kitchen. There, Rio and Miharu were chatting about something as they made the food.

It was a space where only the two of them existed, and for some reason, it felt difficult to intrude on.

What is this I’m feeling...

Aki had a strange sense of déjà vu once again, but she couldn’t pinpoint the reason why, and was overcome with an indescribable feeling of vexation. Watching the two act intimately made her heart sting with pain.

Aki didn’t know that the person who broke his promise — the person who she hated illogically from the depths of her heart — was the same person who had saved her from her crisis earlier. She didn’t know what Rio was feeling right now, as he lived in this moment with his memories of the life he led as Amakawa Haruto, after the current life he had been through.

Not only Aki, but everyone else in this house, too. No one knew.

Fate was a cruel mistress.

◇◇◇

Masato finished his bath just as dinner was finished being prepared.

“Dinner’s ready. Come over here, you two.”

Rio invited Aki and Masato over to the dining table. The table was lined with rice and colorful side dishes like miso soup, karaage, steamed vegetables, chopped burdock root, boiled greens in soy sauce, and salad.

“...Japanese style?” Aki froze at the sight of the dishes on the table. She never imagined she’d be able to eat a Japanese meal in a world that wasn’t Earth.

“Whoa, that looks delicious!” Masato was the polar opposite of Aki, eyes sparkling with no doubts in his mind at all.

“Let’s dig in. Sit wherever you like,” Rio prompted. Everyone made their way to their respective seats of preference. As a result, Rio sat next to Miharu and Masato sat next to Aki, the four of them facing each other across the table.

“Thank you for the meal,” they all said together spontaneously, before beginning to eat.

“Yum! Did you make this, Miharu?” Masato reached for the karaage without hesitation. The steaming-hot fried chicken burst open and released the juices of the meat in his mouth, making Masato beam with a broad smile.

Miharu shook her head. “Nope, Haruto was the one who made it.”

“Wow, Haruto’s amazing. These steamed veggies are delicious, too,” Masato hummed in admiration.

“Miharu made the steamed vegetables. Even though you didn’t have much time to make it, the flavor soaked in perfectly. It’s very delicious,” Rio praised. It was his first time eating Miharu’s homemade cooking ever, so Rio had reached for her dish first without hesitation.

“Thank you very much.” Miharu grinned with embarrassment.

The peaceful atmosphere remained throughout the whole meal.

◇◇◇

Aki and Masato must have been mentally exhausted, as they were immediately overcome with sleepiness once they finished their meals and were able to relax. Rio had been cleaning up the plates with Miharu, but stopped to lead the two to their bedrooms and put them to bed.

Afterward, he immediately returned to finish cleaning. After convincing a reluctant Miharu that he didn’t mind bathing last, he sat down on the sofa in the now-quiet living room.

Sipping at his hot tea, Rio sighed and vacantly reviewed the events that happened that day.

It sure is quiet... When it’s this quiet, it almost feels like everything that happened today was just a dream.

It really was just like a dream — the girl he loved and the little sister he was separated from in his previous life had appeared before him once again. However, it was by no means a dream — Rio had definitely met them in this world; especially Miharu, whom he had wanted to see again more than anything. Even Aki, Haruto’s little sister, was here.

In the bathroom, beyond the door to the changing room, was the girl he loved so much, taking a bath, alone.

Do they... trust me? Or are they simply just unguarded? Rio smiled wryly.

Captured by a man whose language they didn’t understand, they had nearly been made into slaves.

While Rio had no intention of assaulting Miharu, she had no way of knowing that for sure. She showed no outward signs of wariness toward Rio, but perhaps she was feeling uneasy on the inside.

Either way, they’ve been thrown into a completely unknown world, out of the blue. I wouldn’t be surprised if the stress has left any of them feeling mentally unstable... I’ll have to prepare an environment where they can relax, to ease the burden on their minds...

A sorrowful expression appeared on Rio’s face, and he covered it with his right hand in torment. The memories of his past life suddenly resurfaced.

...I wonder if I should tell them the truth... That I have Amakawa Haruto’s memories, Rio pondered to himself.

While it was clear as day that telling them would only cause confusion, Rio wondered if he even wanted to do so to begin with.

Amakawa Haruto was dead, after all — that was why Rio had cultivated a sense of finality with his previous self, despite feeling a strong and lingering attachment of his love for Miharu. That is... he was almost able to let Haruto go, until Miharu appeared before him — in the same form as the last time Haruto had seen her.

Honestly, there was no denying that he had nearly succumbed to his inclinations, that perhaps the idle youth he had spent as Amakawa Haruto could be done all over again.

There was a part of him that felt happiness in his reunion with Miharu, looking forward to spending time together even for a short while.

However, it was suffocating at the same time, because Rio considered himself to be a person that could never turn back. He couldn’t turn back.

He had said goodbye to his weakened self, the one that kept running away from a painful reality, in his parents’ homeland. He had decided that he would get his own hands dirty, if necessary, and search for someone that might not even be alive anymore. If he was alive, he’d kill him.

Rio had changed. Amakawa Haruto’s naivety was gone — as a matter of fact, he didn’t even know if he really was Amakawa Haruto anymore. The fact that he had vague memories in his mind was the only proof he had that he still was Haruto.

Today, he had killed someone for the first time in his life. Even at that very moment, with the sensation of killing someone and the warmth of their body still lingering on him, he felt no particular sense of guilt — most likely because the man he had killed deserved it.

At this point, what could he reveal about himself to his three guests? Would he tell Miharu that he had the memories of Amakawa Haruto, then confess his undying love to her?

What if Miharu had someone she loved, and therefore rejected him? Or, even worse — it was possible she might jump to her own conclusions, considering the current situation they had been placed in.

It’s no good. Even if I told them now, Mii-cha... No, Miharu and the others would only be distraught. I only just decided not to place a burden on them anymore, and yet it took me so long to realize what should have been obvious. I guess I still haven’t regained my composure yet... Rio sighed shamefully.

He had no idea why the Miharu that disappeared years before Amakawa Haruto died had appeared in this world as a high school student; he was rather bewildered by it, actually. But he knew what his priority needed to be, for now and for the future: he had to protect Miharu, Aki, and Masato. That much was certain.

I’ll need to teach them the language and the customs... It looks like I’ll be constantly with them for a while. My trip to see Professor Celia will have to be put off until later. Rio decided to sit back and observe the situation for a while.

Just then, the sound of the door to the changing room opening echoed in the living room. Rio directed his gaze to the changing room to see Miharu, fresh from her bath.

Miharu closed the door politely before looking around the living room. She was still in her school uniform, but looked strangely attractive after having just finished her bath.

When Miharu laid her eyes on Rio sitting on the sofa, she approached him with brisk footsteps and bowed her head. “Ah, Haruto. That was a great bath... Thank you for letting me use it first.”

Miharu’s long black hair, so glossy that it shone like varnish, swayed. It tickled Rio’s nostrils with the scent of soap. Rio felt his heart leap in his chest, then shook his head as though dismissing it as a figment of his imagination. “Don’t worry about it. Do you have a moment to talk right now?”

“Yes. I wanted to talk to you too...” Miharu nodded hesitantly.

“Here you go, then.” Rio poured ice tea into an empty mug and offered it to Miharu.

Miharu was feeling thirsty after her bath, so she brought the mug to her mouth softly and smiled happily. “Thank you... It’s delicious.”

Rio immediately refilled Miharu’s mug with more ice tea. “Would you like to go shopping tomorrow?” he asked.

“Shopping... you say?” Miharu cocked her head, her expression blank.

“Yes. I thought we could pick up some necessities for your everyday needs... and... Well, you can’t stay in your uniform forever, so...” Rio said, seemingly reluctant about bringing it up.

“Yes, you’re right,” Miharu said, nodding uncomfortably. Then, her expression shifted, and she gasped. “Ah... W-Was it weird to wear this again after all?! U-Umm, do I stink of sweat or something?” she asked in embarrassment.

Now that she was able to reflect on it, she had worn this outfit while she had prepared dinner and subsequently ate. She had also walked around endlessly in this uniform throughout the day; fearing that the smell of her sweat had soaked through, she sniffed her uniform in a panic to check.

Rio shook his head in shock. “N-No, not at all! You smell really nice! I could breathe in your scent forever.” In his rush to deny her statement, he spoke in a way that could have been taken the wrong way.

“Huh...? Ah... Umm, t-thank you... very much?” Miharu tilted her head; she was rather taken aback. She seemed to interpret the meaning of his words in a positive way, at least.

Rio belatedly realized he had made a remark that could be misunderstood and corrected himself in a hurry. “Ah, I-I didn’t mean it in a weird way! I just meant that it wasn’t a bad smell. I’m sorry!” he said, and bowed his head.

“I-It’s okay, I understand. I-I’m sorry, too.” Miharu bowed her head thankfully in return.

The air between them grew awkward, and for a while, their expressions were of an embarrassed sort. They averted their gazes, looking apologetic.

After the awkward silence between them continued for a few more seconds...

“...And so, I was thinking it’d be a bit difficult to move around with all of us, so would it be okay for you to shop on the behalf of the other two tomorrow? Although it would mean that Aki and Masato have to stay back here alone...” Rio said in a slightly high-pitched voice, returning to their derailed conversation.

“Y-Yes. It’ll be okay.” Miharu nodded willingly. She knew that if the three of them had followed Rio into the city, they would only be a burden with their lack of understanding of the language.

“Then we’ll leave sometime in the morning after breakfast, so please write down a list of the things you need. There’s no need to worry about money, so write down everything you can think of,” Rio said, trying to encourage Miharu to show no restraint in what she wanted.

However, Miharu’s expression clouded apologetically. “Umm... We don’t have anything that would be worth any money, but I swear... One day I will repay you for looking after us like this. Thank you so much. If you ever have any housework or chores you need me to do, just say the word,” she said, bowing her head deeply at Rio.

“No, there’s no need for you to repay me in that way...” Rio scratched at his head, his expression troubled. If he put himself in Miharu’s shoes, he could understand her feelings, but just thinking about it left him feeling conflicted.

“I cannot allow that.” Miharu shook her head resolutely. She seemed to have quite the upright and earnest personality.

“...All right. Then, you can do some of the housework around here, and we’ll call it even between us with that. I will also pay you an allowance for your work.” Rio nodded and smiled faintly.

“Thank you very much. I’ll work hard.” Miharu’s expression continued to remain apologetic.

“Yes, please do. Also, there was something that I had to give you, Miharu. This...” Rio said, taking out the small pouch tightly packed with gold coins.

“Umm... What’s this?” Miharu asked hesitantly, peeking at the glint of gold from the opening of the pouch.

“The compensation money received from the slave merchant that tried to kidnap you and the others.”

“These are gold coins, right? It looks very valuable...”

“Well, to an extent. But, he had nearly ruined your entire lives. This is in no way too high of a price to be considered compensation money. You might not be too happy to accept this money, but please save it in case you need it as backup funds one day,” Rio said slowly to ensure Miharu understood his point.

“...Won’t you take this money instead, Haruto? We were the ones rescued by you, so I couldn’t possibly accept it,” Miharu declared after a pause of consideration, showing no sign of regret in front of such a huge amount of money.

“No, no. This is compensation money, so it has to go to the victims that suffered the crime. That’s how it is.” Rio shook his head, slightly taken aback.

“But we’ve only ever been on the receiving end of your kindness, and won’t have any way to use the money for a while... I would be much happier if you would accept this instead, Haruto,” Miharu emphasized. She chose to stick to her guns rather than receive what was being offered to her. Her stubborn will was clearly obvious.

“...Then we can use this money tomorrow for shopping and buying the living necessities that you’ll need in the near future.” Rio had originally intended to loan them the finances they needed, but he figured he could make a compromise instead.

“But then wouldn’t that end up being money used on us anyway...?”

“And that’s how it should be, since this was the compensation money that was meant for you,” Rio stated clearly.

“Is it really okay?” Miharu asked.

“It’s really okay,” Rio said a bit lightheartedly.

Miharu stared in wonder. “Okay. Thank you very much, Haruto.” She thanked him — for the umpteenth time that day — with a giggle.

With a faint smile at the look of bewilderment on Miharu’s face, Rio turned to call out to Aishia, who had been waiting in the air from some point. “Let’s go, Aishia.”

“Okay.” Aishia closely watched Miharu being carried by Rio, before nodding.

◇◇◇

Miharu watched the endless scenic view from the skies in a daze. “...Wow, we’re really flying through the sky,” she murmured in wonder, several minutes after the flight had begun.

“Is it prettier than the view from the ground?” Rio asked with a smile tugging at his lips.

“It’s gorgeous. I’ve never seen anything so beautiful before,” Miharu answered in a breathy voice, captivated by the picturesque scenery before her.

“I’m glad to hear that. It’ll be a while until we reach our destination city, so feel free to enjoy it all you want. You’ll see a lot of different types of scenery on the way.”

“Yes!” Nodding happily, Miharu’s eyes darted about as she enjoyed the view.

Seeing her made Rio shift his gaze, too, and he similarly enjoyed the scenery. At the end of his line of sight was the ridgeline of the mountains and the surfaces of the lakes in the distance; they sparkled from the rays of sun shining between the clouds. They continued at that leisurely pace for half an hour or so until they reached their destination of Amande.

“Aishia. We can’t descend right into the city, so we’re stopping in the forest instead.”

“Got it,” Aishia replied, and they they landed together in the forest.

“Sorry, Miharu. We’ll be going on foot from here. The ground is hard to walk on, so I’ll carry you until we reach the road,” Rio said.

The area was covered in dense vegetation and mossy undergrowth, making the footing terrible for walking on. While Miharu had an overcoat on, she was wearing her uniform skirt and leather shoes underneath, which would make the journey difficult.

“O-Okay. Thank you,” Miharu replied, nodding nervously.

“I’ll be running a little, so it may be a little bumpier than when we were flying. Be careful not to bite your tongue. Let’s go, Aishia,” Rio said to Miharu and Aishia, before making a gentle leap forward. Despite the fact that he was carrying Miharu, he was crossing several meters in a single stride.

“W-Wow. Amazing... Is this a type of sorcery, too?” Quietly tightening her grip around Rio, Miharu widened her eyes at what was clearly a display of superhuman abilities. Aishia was also following behind Rio with agile movements.

“I’ve enhanced my physical body and abilities through a technique called spirit arts. I’m also giving myself a little push by controlling the wind to help my movement and landing. Let me know if it’s too fast for you,” Rio said out of consideration for Miharu.

Miharu shook her head calmly. “I’m fine. It’s not even shaking that much.”

The group arrived at the road leading to Amande only a few minutes later. After checking there was no one else around, Rio gently lowered Miharu to the ground and handed her a necklace. “Before we go into the city, please put this on.”

“Okay. What is it...?”

“An artifact that changes your hair color — people with black hair will draw attention around here. It’ll return to normal once you remove the necklace, so there’s no need for any concern about that.”

“I understand,” Miharu said, nodding, then put on the necklace as requested. Once she did, the necklace automatically started to absorb Miharu’s essence and instantly changed her hair color.

“...Wow, it really changed.”

“It suits you. ...Just so you know, the city we’re about to head to is called Amande. Shall we go now?” Rio complimented Miharu shyly before starting to walk at a relaxed pace. Miharu and Aishia followed after him.

Ten minutes later, they were out of the forest and had reached Amande.

Miharu gazed in wonder. “...There’s a lot of people.”

They had entered the city to find huge bustling crowds, as the morning markets were still open. Stalls were lined everywhere, overflowing with clamoring liveliness.

“This is a trade city, so it’s particularly busy. Most of the kingdom is uninhabited land, so people tend to swarm cities like this,” Rio explained.

“I see... I’ll have to be careful so I won’t get lost,” Miharu said with a mix of awe and worry as she watched everyone making their way around the crowds.

“Don’t worry. Miharu should just do this,” Aishia said, then suddenly grabbed Rio’s left hand.

“Umm...” Rio showed a look of bewilderment as Miharu blushed with embarrassment.

“Now we won’t get lost,” Aishia offered simply. She was right, but both Rio and Miharu were too overcome with embarrassment to reach for each other’s hands.

“You’re not going to hold it?” Aishia tilted her head in question. Her expression made them doubt themselves, wondering if they were the weird ones for being so self-conscious.

“Ahaha. Then... excuse me.” With a bemused smile, Miharu softly took Rio’s hand.

“Let’s go.” Aishia nudged Rio — making Rio chuckle with a smile — then the three of them finally set off.

However, both Miharu and Aishia were both incredibly beautiful girls that instantly drew the attention of the men around. They sent glares filled with hatred and envy at Rio, as he was holding both their hands.

“...Haha... Okay, you two — put on your hoods. It seems like we’re standing out,” Rio suggested with a twitch in his face, unable to withstand the gazes.

◇◇◇

In the central business district of Amande...

“Apparently, this store has all the daily necessities for women,” Rio explained to Miharu and Aishia as he stood in front of a towering building. He had asked a female stall owner if there were any shops that stocked all the necessities a woman would need; it was fine if it was a higher price as long as it was of a decent quality. All the female stall owners had pointed to this store.

“What a wonderful building...” Miharu said as she looked up at the four-story building.

“It’s called the Ricca Guild, and it’s a direct branch of the trade guild that’s famous even in the neighboring kingdoms. The governor of this city, Liselotte, is also the president of the Ricca Guild.”

There were several stores owned by the Ricca Guild in Amande; the city could even be considered the base for the guild.

This store should have all kinds of useful items in stock.

Rio recalled the last time he had visited Amande several years ago. Specifically, the rumor he had heard when he dropped by the city on his way from Strahl to Yagumo.

Yes — Rio unilaterally knew about the girl named Liselotte. The talented young woman was the daughter of Duke Cretia, the great lord of the Kingdom of Galarc. She was also the first person to bring the processed food “pasta” into this world. It was clear that Liselotte, or perhaps a person working with her in the shadows, was using knowledge from Earth.

The scale of the Ricca Guild had grown exponentially in the few years Rio was away from the Strahl region. It had even become a leading trade guild in several neighboring kingdoms as well; they would have certainly developed numerous new products in the last few years.

There was no way for Rio to make the daily life items modern Japanese women used, so this was the perfect solution for Miharu to do her shopping.

Just before they entered the building, Rio spoke up. “Okay, I’m leaving the rest to you two. I’ll come back to this store in around an hour. Just leave any interpreting to Aishia.”

Since it was a branch specializing in female-targeted products, it was difficult for Rio to enter as a male. She probably needed to buy underwear and other such things, so he figured it would be easiest to leave the chaperoning to Aishia.

“O-Okay...” Miharu nodded timidly.

“Aishia, please take care of Miharu... And make sure you don’t leave this store.”

“Yup, leave it to me.” Aishia gave a sincere nod.

...Well, I’m sure it’ll be fine. They wouldn’t be able to shop at their own pace with me around anyway.

Rio decided to trust the two of them. While he still had some concerns, he knew he couldn’t be too overprotective. The store’s security seemed reliable enough that the chance of strange customers would be low.

“See you later, then.”

With that, Rio let go of Miharu and Aishia’s hands.

◇◇◇

After parting ways with the girls, Rio began to gather information in the area around the building where Miharu was shopping.

Information spread slowly in this world, as the methods of communication weren’t very advanced. Because of that, the most well-informed people were nobles, merchants, and guild members. They took in all kinds of information because of their contact with large numbers of people, as well as their ability to collude with others like themselves to create their own intelligence network. That was why common folk, like Rio, were unable to gain much information by just remaining passive. In order to find the information he wanted, he either had to be in contact with many people on a daily basis or proactively approach those with the knowledge.

At present, Rio was effectively gathering information by going around the stalls and talking to the merchants. He wasn’t part of a guild and had no noble acquaintances, so the only way he could gather information was through the merchants available to him. By purchasing their products and chatting them up under the guise of a casual conversation, the merchants were more willing to talk. While he wasn’t likely to gain any information of high secrecy or reliability, his efforts would likely be fruitful nonetheless.

Rio visited a stall that sold grilled skewers and ordered a fair amount before addressing the female store owner. “Has anything of importance happened recently? I was really surprised when those pillars of light appeared the other day.”

“Oh my, haven’t you heard? People say that was the sign of the hero appearing,” the stall owner replied as she grilled the meat.

“The... hero?” The word hero took Rio by surprise, making him widen his eyes.

“You know of the sacred prophecy at least, right? The one about the great hero that appears alongside the six pillars of light. Since the exact events of that prophecy occurred, the rumor is that the hero has appeared, too.”

“Right, there was something like that. I see...” Rio nodded with comprehension.

The people of the Strahl region believed in the deities known as the Six Wise Gods. While Rio himself was not a man of faith, he had received classes during his time in the Royal Academy, so he could still vaguely remember the details of the sacred texts.

It might be related to how Miharu and the others appeared in this world... Or maybe they were dragged into the fray? If so, does that mean the two people with them... are the heroes? Rio thought, immediately breaking down the information and making his own hypothesis.

“Was there anything else that stood out recently around here? I was thinking of going to the Kingdom of Beltrum in the near future...”

“Hmm... They had a slightly larger scale skirmish with the Proxia Empire to the north just a while ago, but that’s just business as usual.” The female stall owner hummed as she answered, then remembered something. “Oh, that’s right. If you’re heading to the Beltrum Kingdom, then you’ll have to pass through the western road, right?”

“Yes, that’s right.” In Rio’s case, he would be flying over it with spirit arts, but he nodded anyway.

“Several adventurers have gone missing recently after heading out on missions along the west road. It isn’t unheard of for people of their line of work to run away, but even skilled adventurers went missing, so it’s been a bit of a hot topic. You look young, but your outfit says you’re an adventurer, too. Be careful out there.”

“...I see, thank you very much.” Rio thanked her and carefully stored their conversation away in his head.

After that, the stall owner continued to chat up Rio even without his prompting; she was a rather talkative person, something that Rio was grateful for since his aim was to gather information. However, most of her chatter was unrelated to the topics he was interested in, so Rio decided to wrap up their talk and retreat when she started to bring up the desire to introduce her daughter to him.

Rio went around a few more stalls afterward, but was unable to gather any new information before he returned to Miharu and Aishia.

◇◇◇

Rio currently stood before the Ricca Guild’s store.

Hmm... I said I’d be back after an hour, but is it okay to just walk in? It was a store that specialized in a wide range of daily items for women; as a man, it almost felt like a forbidden holy ground, making him fearful of intruding.

At that moment, Aishia stepped out of the store by herself. Miharu was nowhere to be seen.

“Huh... Aishia? Where’s Miharu?”

“Haruto returned, so I came out to get you. Miharu is still shopping,” Aishia replied succinctly.

“Oh, okay. But... how did you know I came back?”

“We’re connected by a path, so I know when you’re close by.”

“I see... Come to think of it, Sara and the other spirit folk mentioned something like that.”

Rio tried to remember what they had said about contract spirits when he was in the village — something about how the contract owner and contract spirit were deeply and spiritually connected by a path. Aishia had only just awakened, but Rio wondered curiously if she would become more sensitive in terms of their connection as more time passed.

“Miharu will become concerned, so let’s go back quickly.” Aishia grabbed Rio’s hand and tried to go back inside the store.

“Right, yeah. Umm, is it... okay if I go in, too?”

Well, it should be fine with Aishia there, Rio thought, allowing himself to be dragged along. If there was an issue, he could just leave again anyway.

Surprisingly, he could spot some other men that were accompanying women inside the store. Each of them seemed rather uncomfortable to be there — Rio could empathize.

When Rio and Aishia entered the store, the gazes of the men who had been standing by as chaperones were naturally drawn to Aishia’s beauty. However, the women they were accompanying keenly noticed the change in the men and sent them a few admonishing signs, such as clearing their throats and the like. The men awkwardly pretended like they hadn’t been staring, even though they were still sneaking looks. Perhaps a similar thing had been happening while Rio was out gathering information too.

“Miharu is on the fourth floor.”

Aishia ignored the looks from all the men and guided Rio. Their linked hands must have stood out, as the attention of both men and women in the store was on them. The men were shooting glares of envy at Rio, while the women seemed to be staring at his face in admiration.

“Oh my, she had someone with her.”

“Hmm...”

“Well, he suits her, at least.”

The voices of the women could be heard throughout the store.

Awkward... Rio felt an extreme sense of discomfort.

The gazes never really left them, so he focused on watching Aishia’s back silently as he moved his feet. They climbed the stairs until they arrived at the fourth floor.

“We’re here.”

Hearing Aishia’s voice, Rio finally looked around at his surroundings again. He was met with the sight of:

“...Huh? Ah...”

A lingerie shop.

There were no men chaperoning this time, as was to be expected, and the women present were all selecting underwear that suited them as they pleased. Miharu was among them. She stood right in front of Rio and stared at undergarments with a serious expression. In her hand was a cute and stylish bra with a modest amount of lace on it.

“Miharu,” Aishia called out.

“Oh, Ai-chan. Where were you? Ah, Haruto’s back too... now...” Miharu looked away from the underwear and toward the direction of Aishia’s voice. Rio was also there, holding Aishia’s hand. He made eye contact with Miharu.

Miharu attempted to greet Rio with a smile when she realized there was something crucially wrong with the situation. She froze on the spot.

The underwear in Miharu’s hands entered Rio’s vision, causing him to apologize while looking away. “S-Sorry.”

“Eh, ah...?!” Miharu finally understood the situation and hid the underwear in her hands in a panic. Her cheeks turned bright red.

“Umm, I’m sorry. Really,” Rio said, apologizing once more. He immediately tried to let go of Aishia’s hand and turn on his heel, but she had a surprisingly strong grip on him, so he couldn’t move. All he could do was bow his head and stare at the floor instead.

“Ah, umm, m-me too!” Miharu lowered her head at Rio in return.

As they were exchanging bows, a female store attendant must have become suspicious, as she called out to them. “Is something the matter?”

“The three of us came here to shop,” Aishia summarized in a flat voice, then looked at Rio’s face and linked hands with him. That was enough to convince the store attendant.

“Oh, I see. That’s fine, then; accompanying gentlemen aren’t forbidden from entering or anything. There are many customers who wish to bring them along and ask for their opinions, too,” she said, shaking her head with an understanding smile.

At some point, they had caught the attention of the other women in the lingerie shop. They had caught wind of the situation and were giggling to themselves.

“I-I’ll come back in another hour. A-Aishia, let go of my hand...” Rio said, quickly retreating from the lingerie shop after he got Aishia to unlink their hands.

I think I’ll write a letter to Professor Celia... I need to tell her that I’ll be late. I’ll definitely go see her, though...

Once he stepped outside the store, he walked to the Ricca Guild branch that handled deliveries.

◇◇◇

Roughly one hour later, Rio once again returned to the building where Miharu was shopping. They either must have just finished their shopping, or Aishia had sensed his approach, as the two of them came outside to meet him.

When Miharu’s eyes met Rio’s, she blushed with embarrassment. Rio grimaced uncomfortably.

“I’m sorry for the lack of consideration I showed earlier,” Rio apologized.

“N-No, I’m the one who should have been more careful. You were brought along by Ai-chan, after all. Ahaha... I’d appreciate it if you could forget everything.” Miharu laughed embarrassedly and shook her head; it was a commendable effort on her part to put the encounter behind them.

“Y-Yes. That aside, it doesn’t look like you have any bags. Did you finish your shopping?”

“Ah, the shop said they’d hold onto the bags. We can pick them up on our way home.”

“I see... That’s a useful service. Let’s go shopping for Masato’s clothes, then.”

Miharu nodded at Rio’s suggestion. “Yes, please.” They had somehow managed to clear the awkward air between them.

Suddenly, Aishia reached for Rio’s left hand and held it. Rio smiled at how natural the movement was for them now.

“Umm, may... may I take your right hand?” Miharu asked Rio shyly.

“...Yes. We wouldn’t want to get separated,” Rio agreed bashfully.

Thus, the three headed for the next store, holding hands. They found a decent shop for men’s clothing in a matter of minutes and went inside to pick out clothes for Masato. Miharu examined all the clothes carefully to select something good for Masato, when she suddenly found clothing that looked good for Haruto.

“This one looks like it’d suit you, Haruto.”

“R-Really?”

“Yes. Could you try holding it up to yourself? ...Ah, see, it really does suit you.”

She handed the clothes over for Rio to hold, then stepped back to look at him from a distance with a beaming smile. Rio smiled in return, appearing somewhat bashful.

“Thank you very much. I am lacking in everyday clothes, so I think I’ll get this.”

Since Rio usually wore combat clothing or semi-combat clothing that could also act as casual attire, he didn’t have many articles that served as solely for everyday wear. This was the perfect opportunity to amend that.

“Umm, then would it be better to buy a few more pieces?”

“Sure. Since you’re here, could I ask you to help me pick them? I’m not very good at choosing clothes...” Rio requested with a wry smile.

“If you’re okay with that, then...” Miharu nodded hesitantly, then began to select clothes not only for Masato, but Rio as well. She had a good sense of style, and made sure to coordinate Rio’s clothes to suit each other.

Time passed by in a flash. “Thank you very much, Miharu. We’ve gotten some good shopping done, thanks to you,” Rio said after he finished buying their items.

“No, I should be thanking you. I had a lot of fun today.”

“I’m happy to hear that. Once your language studies have progressed a bit, we should come here again with Aki and Masato as a breather... Since the plan is to stay where we are for another month, at least.”

After they learned a fair amount of the language, he might bring them to the spirit folk village. Nonetheless, it would probably require further discussion first.

“Yes, please!” Miharu said, smiling happily.

◇◇◇

Rio and the girls were able to return to the rock house in the field before the sun had set. They ate dinner and then settled down to enjoy tea together, when Rio suddenly spoke up.

“Actually, I may have gained some plausible information today about the two people you were with just before you were brought to this world. It’s not bad news, either.”

“R-Really?!” Aki stammered, immediately drawn to Rio’s words.

“More or less, yes. It wouldn’t be very trustworthy information under normal circumstances, and it doesn’t help us with their location, unfortunately.” Rio shrugged his shoulders and nodded.

“So, what did you find out about the two of them?” Aki pressed impatiently.

Rio smiled faintly. “The two of them... may have become heroes, I guess,” he explained in a frank manner. Aki couldn’t help but doubt what she had heard.

“...Huh?” she asked.

Not only did Aki doubt what she was hearing, but Miharu and Masato also had expressions of astonishment. Their reactions were understandable; heroes weren’t a common career path for a modern day Japanese person, after all.

“Well, I guess that’s the normal reaction to have.” Rio watched the reaction of the three Earthlings with his usual wry smile. Meanwhile, Aishia breathed a small and sleepy yawn from where she sat beside him.

“Hey, Haruto. By hero, do you mean something like the main character of a video game?” Masato asked hesitantly.

“It’s probably exactly like that, I believe.”

“Huh... Seriously? Bro as a hero, you say... I guess I kind of get it, but it doesn’t suit him at all!” Masato said with a somewhat amused grimace.

“This world has religious beliefs, too, and the sacred texts speak of a prophecy where the heroes are summoned. The phenomenon in that prophecy came true at nearly the same time you three were dragged into this world. That’s why a rumor is circulating that heroes have appeared in the Strahl region.”

“And those heroes are Satsuki and Takahisa?” Miharu asked.

“Yes. The prophecy claims there are six heroes, so I believe they must be two of them. The event that occurred was on a large enough scale for it to be just that.”

Though Rio had been too distracted by the feminine voice in his head to look at them directly, the six pillars of light that had appeared in that moment had scattered a tremendous amount of ode and mana — enough for him to believe that heroes could indeed be summoned from another world.

“Then... would we be able to meet the two of them if we find out where all the heroes are?!” Aki asked expectantly.

“If my hypothesis is right, then yes. The prophecy said the heroes would appear by the Sacred Stones, but who knows where those Sacred Stones are,” Rio replied with a troubled look. There was a lot of information readily available about the location of the Sacred Stones, but it was normal to assume all of it was misleading or false.

“That can’t be...” Aki’s face darkened in frustration.

“It’s okay. They have to be somewhere in Strahl, so as long as we keep waiting, more rumors of the heroes will circulate eventually. It’s best if we just wait patiently. Of course, I’ll do what I can to find out more about the Sacred Stones and heroes, but I’d like the three of you to focus on learning the language for now. Is that all right with you, Miharu?” Rio looked at her for a response.

“Yes. We’ll be placing all the burden on you, Haruto, but please take care of us,” Miharu agreed apologetically.

“Then, that’s decided — you’ll start learning the language from tomorrow. It may get a bit rigorous at times, but the harder you work, the faster you’ll learn. You’ll eventually be able to put more time into other things. Let’s all do our best!” Rio said to the others to motivate them.

“Yes, please teach us well!” Aki said energetically, fired up by his words.

“Studying, huh... Even though we’ve come to another world, the things we have to do haven’t changed...” Masato sighed and grumbled to himself.

“Masato, I’m warning you now. If you don’t do this properly, I’ll be angry.”

“I know!” Masato nodded bitterly at Aki’s warning. He was aware that this was a necessary task, at the very least.

Miharu watched the two of them with a pleasant smile.

◇◇◇

After that, Rio worked together with Miharu and Aishia to clean everything up. They would begin their language studies in the morning, so Aki and Masato were sent off to bed early.

“Good work, Miharu... And you, too, Aishia. We should go to sleep soon too,” Rio said to the two girls at the dining table.

Miharu bowed. “Okay. Thank you for everything today, Haruto. You too, Ai-chan,” she said, looking at Aishia.

“Good work, Miharu,” Aishia replied sleepily.

“Ahaha. You look sleepy, Aishia — let’s go to bed right away. Good night!”

Rio figured that if he stuck around any longer he’d just be keeping Miharu and Aishia awake with him, so he started to walk toward his room.

“Good night,” Aishia said, before following after Rio. Miharu bid them good night, before walking off to her own room.

“Wait, huh? A-Ai-chan, isn’t your room next to mine? It’s just Haruto’s room in that direction. Aren’t you going to bed?” Miharu found something odd about the direction Aishia was heading and called out to stop her.

“Aishia?” Rio said with wide eyes, wondering what was the matter.

“I’m going to sleep.” Aishia cocked her head blankly.

“Umm... Where?” Rio asked nervously.

“In Haruto’s room.”

“E-Eeh?!” Miharu exclaimed in shock at Aishia’s reply.

“Umm... You have your own room, though. You’re supposed to sleep there,” Rio said carefully to Aishia, holding his head in his right hand.

“I sleep with Haruto,” Aishia declared in a pure and innocent manner.

“N-No, you can’t do that,” Rio declined in a panic, but Aishia only seemed to be curious as to why that was.

“Why not?”

“Well, that’s because...”

It seemed as though she was unfamiliar with the subtleties of personal boundaries between a man and a woman. Rio was left at a loss for words as he looked at Miharu for assistance.

“Ah, umm. You know, Ai-chan... It’s a little problematic — rather, unfavorable — for a man and a woman to sleep together in the same room if they’re not in an intimate relationship,” Miharu explained tactfully, trying to save Rio from his dilemma.

“Why?”

“U-Umm...” Aishia’s childlike question left Miharu the one at a loss for words this time. It was surprisingly difficult to explain the common sense rules and morals that applied to human society using words. Simply saying that it wasn’t allowed wasn’t enough for a spirit like Aishia to understand.

Aishia looked at Miharu with innocent eyes. “Aren’t Haruto and I intimately related?”

“Ah, erm, that’s not what I mean.”

Intimate? What was intimate? Why were the right words so hard to choose? Despite trying her best, Miharu was at an utter loss.

“If we can’t sleep as just the two of us, then do you want to join in, too?” Aishia suggested.

“T-That’s even more impossible!” Miharu turned red and shook her head.

“Why?”

“Huh? Ah, because... I-I have someone I love already. Ah — no, wait, t-that doesn’t mean I hate Haruto by any means, though!” Miharu was babbling incoherently and replying to everything with foolish honesty.

“...Yes, I know. Haha.”

Hearing that Miharu had someone she loved had been a mild shock to Rio, but he somehow managed to keep a smile on his face. He had marginally suspected such a thing already.

“I don’t get it,” Aishia murmured quietly to herself. Rio sighed and smiled wryly. “...Why do you want to sleep with me anyway, Aishia?”

“I can replenish ode more efficiently by Haruto’s side. It’s also more comfortable,” Aishia answered. The second part aside, it was a surprisingly logical reason.

“Oh, replenishing essence. That’s true... But if you’re a spirit, you should be able to take on an astral form as well, right? Wouldn’t you be able to suppress the depletion of your essence more in that state...?”

Since Aishia had a humanoid form, it felt so natural for her to be physically materialized that Rio had forgotten that spirits normally preferred to exist in their astral form. Materializing and maintaining a physical form expended a certain amount of magic essence, so it was an extremely inefficient use of their energy.

“Astral... form?” Miharu asked, unable to keep up with the conversation.

“She has a physical body right now, but at their core, spirits are actually embodiments of mana. So, like their name suggests, they have a spiritual form. Normally, they are unperceivable to humans — that form is called the astral form.”

“...I-I see. Then Ai-chan can take on that astral form, too?” Miharu seemed slightly dubious as she looked at Aishia.

“I can.” Aishia nodded. Her body suddenly turned to fine particles of light and dispersed in the blink of an eye.

“S-She disappeared? Ai-chan?” Miharu’s eyes widened in shock as she hesitantly called Aishia’s name.

“I’m here,” Aishia replied; the particles of light gathered together to take on her form once more.

Miharu made a noise of wonder and turned to Rio for confirmation. “Wah... T-That was the astral form just now?”

“Yes. You won’t be able to see her or physically interact with her, but she still exists there in her astral form. Spirits expend essence by simply existing, so they use much less energy when in their astral form.”

Miharu looked at Aishia. “I understand... Ah, then if you stayed in your astral form on a regular basis, you wouldn’t need to sleep together with Haruto anymore... is that right?”

“Essence recovery isn’t that big of a deal. I will replenish essence more efficiently the closer I am to Haruto, but if I don’t use any spirit arts, then it isn’t that difficult for me to stay in physical form even without Haruto nearby,” Aishia explained logically with a shake of her head.

“Umm, then, do you still need to sleep together with Haruto...?”

“Yes. I want to be with Haruto.”

“A-Ahaha. Really... Ah, then, how about... you sleep with Haruto in your astral form? How about that instead?” Miharu suggested, looking at Rio with a strained smile.

“Umm... I guess, yeah. That should be, well... all right, I suppose?” Rio nodded with uncertainty, though he wasn’t quite sure if doing that actually solved the moral issue of a man and woman sleeping together in the same room. At least no physical mishaps could occur while she was invisible in her astral form.

Aishia seemed pretty stubborn over the whole thing herself, making it nearly impossible to convince her otherwise. It was only a makeshift solution at best, but it was a safe line to draw as a compromise.

“Are you okay with that, Ai-chan?” Miharu asked.

“Sure.” Aishia nodded quietly.

Thus, it was decided that Aishia would sleep in Rio’s room in her astral form. And if Rio woke up to her sleeping in her physical form the next morning — well, that was a story for another day.

However, the dark monster held a hand against its abdomen as it staggered back to its feet. It didn’t seem able to comprehend what had happened.

“Guuargh, aurgh?” it groaned curiously.

What was that texture just now? That monster was rock-hard. It seemed to have received some damage, but it still stood up after taking the hit... Even though I attacked it with the intention of incapacitating it... Rio observed the dark creature with wide eyes.

Meanwhile, Aishia approached and apologized with a regretful expression. “...Haruto, I’m sorry. Everyone was in danger.”

“No, I’m sure you would have made it on time, Aishia. I may have stuck my neck in where it wasn’t needed, but I’m glad it seems like I got back at just the right time. Sorry, you two. I came back late...” Rio shook his head with a strained smile, then looked at Miharu and Aki behind him.

“Ah, H-Haruto... Miharu, Haruto’s here.” Aki sighed in relief. Miharu timidly opened her eyes, having squeezed them shut, and turned around. “Haruto...” she called in a daze.

She looked up at his face with befuddled eyes; it was Rio’s first time seeing her with such an expression.

“Everything’s all right now,” Rio said gently, pulling Miharu by the hand to help her stand up.

“...T-Thank you very much. Ah, s-sorry.” Miharu accepted Rio’s hand and stood up, but her knees still seemed to be weak. She staggered forward and leaned into him. He supported her in his arms, blushing with embarrassment. In the meantime, Aki stood up by herself.

“Aki, can I leave Miharu to you? The battle isn’t over yet, so you two go inside the house. It’ll be over quickly,” Rio said with a wry smile.

“O-Okay.” Aki nodded hesitantly before approaching Rio and supporting Miharu in Rio’s place.

Within a few seconds, Miharu and Aki had stepped inside the house, the door slamming shut behind them.

“Aishia, do you know what they are?” he asked Aishia, observing the three strangely shaped creatures once he had confirmed that Miharu and Aki had gone inside.

“I don’t know, but... it feels like they’re of a monster class. Also, the black one is probably strong,” Aishia explained broadly.

“I see. But they’re wounded already... though they still seem quite energetic.”

As Rio and Aishia quickly exchanged information, the black monster had already regained most of its vitality. It stood on two legs as it glared at them aggressively.

“The gray one I attacked seems to have recovered, too,” Aishia said, looking at the gray monster she had sent flying earlier.

“It doesn’t matter if they’re just naturally strong or have some kind of abnormal ability to recover; what we have to do doesn’t change. I’ll clean up the rest of them, so you stand back, Aishia.”

“Haruto, you don’t have to worry about me. It doesn’t matter if the opponents are human shaped or real humans, I won’t show any mercy to someone who stands in your way.” Aishia shook her head resolutely.

Rio hesitated for several moments. “...I see. Let’s split up and deal with them, then. I’ll take the black one... Can I leave the gray ones to you, Aishia?” he asked Aishia with a sigh.

“Of course,” Aishia nodded quietly.

“Guaargh!” The black monster seemed to have resolved to flee instead; it let out a loud roar to signal its retreat. In response, the gray ones groaned and turned on their heels to run away, too.

Do they have the intelligence to know to run away from opponents they can’t win against? With widened eyes, Rio watched their retreating forms.

Rio and Aishia’s forms disappeared from where they had stood, as they instantly closed in on the black and gray creatures respectively, moving in to attack.

“Gargh?!” When Rio appeared before the black monster, he twisted the enemy’s body and slammed it against the ground. It didn’t seem to have much effect, as the black monster got back up using its incredible reflexes, immediately moving to counterattack.

It’s fast, but... Its movements are linear and its attacks are wide open.

Rio easily dodged the attack and drove his knee into the solar plexus he had wounded earlier.

“Gruh?” The black monster’s body lifted up into the air. Rio grabbed his opponent’s feet and swung it around, dislocating its joints as he smashed it into the ground. The black monster let out a pained groan.

“You sure are tough. Can you understand what I’m saying?” Rio asked, stepping on the abdomen of the black creature. Despite its different skin color, its shape was still human-like, so he wondered if it was possible to communicate with it.

“Gruuuugh.” The monster could only give a low groan.

...No good, huh? What is this guy, anyway? Well, if it’s a monster, it’d leave an enchanted gem, I guess.

With a sigh, Rio drew the blade at his waist. He had never seen nor heard of a monster like this before; in order to check whether it actually was a monster or not, Rio thrust his sword through the black creature’s heart.

“Gragh!” The black creature yelled louder than ever as it struggled wildly. Even with a sword through its heart, it was still moving around. It had quite the stamina.

Somewhat shocked, Rio looked down at the black monster writhing in pain. Eventually, the black creature’s struggling slowed down. “Please kill me,” it seemed to mouth slowly.

With widened eyes, Rio took in the movements of its mouth, then ended the black monster’s life. With a clean snapping noise, its body started to break down into dust, leaving behind a huge heart-shaped blue gem.

So, it was a monster. But the way its mouth moved at the end... Rio picked up the enchanted gem left behind by the strange monster with a conflicted expression.

“Haruto, I’m done here, too.” Aishia walked over with two enchanted gems in her hands. Her expression was so pure, it was as though her brutal mindset from earlier had been washed away entirely.

“...Thank you, Aishia. Shall we go inside? There’s something I need to tell you.” With a small smile, Rio led Aishia back inside the house.

◇◇◇

“I-I’m so sorry!”

Once Rio and Aishia stepped inside, Aki bowed her head, her face completely pale.

“Umm, why are you apologizing?” Rio asked, taken aback.

“Umm... Even though you said not to leave the house without a good reason, I went outside and caused Miharu to put herself in danger...”

“No, no... What happened just now was a pretty irregular event. But, well... Why did you go outside?” Rio asked with a troubled look.

Miharu defended Aki in a hurry. “U-Umm, it was my fault! I was being inconsiderate of Aki’s feelings and made her angry...”

“That’s not true! I... I... I’m sorry! I’m so sorry, Miharu. I’m sorry...” Tears started to stream down Aki’s face as she spoke, clinging to Miharu, who gently patted Aki on the back with a distraught expression.

“It doesn’t seem like I need to say anything more,” Rio said with a smile.

“Mm... Oh? Haruto’s back. Huh, are you crying, Aki?” A sleepy Masato appeared in the living room with a big yawn.

“I-I’m not! You carefree dummy!” Aki separated from Miharu in a fluster, turning away with a huff.

Masato tilted his head and peered at Aki’s face. “Hmm?”

“...That aside, it’s been decided that we’re moving,” Rio said, changing the subject rather forcefully out of consideration for Aki.

“Ooh, really?!” Masato asked, his attention diverted away from Aki to Rio.

“Yes. I’m sure it’s been stressful for you, being unable to go outside freely... and it must have been boring, but you’ll be able to live your lives comfortably in another location instead.”

“It’s true that all the studying has left my body all stiff... Wait, when are we moving?”

“I’m thinking tomorrow, maybe. But there are a few rules that have to be cleared up before we move. Let’s go over the details while we eat some snacks, shall we?” Rio said, then walked into the kitchen.

◇◇◇

The next morning, the five set out for the spirit folk village.

“We’ll move to our new location, now. The scenery before you will change in an instant, just like when you came to this world. It isn’t dangerous, though, so just relax,” Rio said to a rather nervous group after putting the stone house away into the Time-Space Cache.

“No... Actually, it’s more like we’re nervous wondering what the other people are like,” Masato said in an unusually flustered manner for him.

The other party they were about to meet were something else, after all. Everyone had received a clear explanation about the spirit folk and their village yesterday; elves, dwarves, and werebeasts — they were all beings that the fantasy-loving Masato was very familiar with, and something he admired greatly. There was no way he wouldn’t be nervous.

“They’re all amazingly nice people, so you’ll make friends in no time. Now, let’s go. Are we all ready?” Rio said with a smile, looking over at everyone.

“Yes, please,” Miharu replied in a somewhat stiff voice, followed by Aki and Masato nodding in response.

“I’m ready anytime,” Aishia agreed with her usual completely relaxed tone.

“Then, here we go. Transilio!” With a smile, Rio activated the teleportation crystal in his hand.

The air began to twist and bend intensely, enveloping the group. In the very next moment, they had disappeared from their original location and teleported to a place near the spirit folk village.

“O-Ooh... Yeah, this was it! This was the feeling I had when my vision suddenly warped back then...” Masato said, glancing around at his surroundings. Miharu and Aki’s eyes were wandering about, too.

“There are many strange presences... they’re similar to mine,” Aishia inclined her head and murmured.

“That’s probably the spirits of the village — it seems like spirits can sense each other’s presence. The shyer spirits are good at suppressing their aura, but there are many spirits in the village,” Rio said, taking a guess at the origin of what Aishia was feeling.

“There’s a spirit with a really big aura.”

“That’s probably Dryas. A humanoid spirit like you, Aishia.”

“There’s another one... not Dryas, but another pretty big spirit is approaching this way,” Aishia said, then looked up at the sky. At the end of her line of sight was Orphia’s contract spirit, Ariel, closing in at a fairly rapid speed.

Aki’s gaze fixed on Ariel’s approach. “...A bird?”

“Isn’t it pretty big? There are people riding on it...” Masato said with a dazed expression. While they were staring, Ariel’s figure grew larger and larger, before finally arriving in the air above Rio’s group. Ariel circled in the air as she began to lower her flight speed.

“There are... girls riding on it,” Miharu murmured.

“They’re all my very close friends, and —” Rio began to explain to Miharu, when one girl jumped off of Ariel first.

It was Latifa. She glanced at the faces of the newcomers, and her expression faltered for a moment. “...Welcome back, Onii-chan!”

She quickly took a breath to ready herself and ran at Rio, crashing into him with a hug.

◇◇◇

One afternoon, a bit before the sun set, somewhere in Strahl...

Reiss stood in the shadows of the forest that extended through the western outskirts of Amande. Surrounding him were several hideous monsters and men, who appeared to be adventurers, lying unconscious.

“...One squad didn’t return. Don’t tell me they were defeated... Defeating a squad of Revenants, especially with an enhanced body in the mix, is no simple feat,” Reiss muttered dubiously.

My actions were a little flashy this time... the investigation squad from the city should be formed soon. Reiss tapped a hand against his mouth in thought, before letting out an annoyed sigh.

“Good grief. I guess I should lie low and keep an eye on things for a while... I’ve also been invited to Charles Arbor’s wedding ceremony in two month’s time. His bride is Celia Claire, if I recall... How a dimwit like that snagged such a catch is beyond me,” he spat bitterly, before turning his gaze to the unconscious adventurers.

“...While the plan will have to be delayed for a while, the numbers have fallen. I guess I shall have to change the materials I have right here and now... How many will remain this time, I wonder?” Reiss grinned like a demon as he slowly walked toward the unconscious adventurers.

Interlude: Summoning A Hero?! Sakata Hiroaki On The Scene!

Meanwhile, just before Miharu and the others found themselves in another world...

His name was Sakata Hiroaki; he was a 19-year-old Japanese young man with an average appearance. While he was in a highly-ranked group at his prep school, he failed his university entrance examinations and became even more of a shut-in, then immersed himself in all sorts of indoor hobbies instead — just like any normal young man would.

On one fine spring day, Hiroaki was lying on his bed in his parents’ house and playing with his PC tablet. He idly visited his favorite websites, watched videos, read novels, played games, and posted on forums to his heart’s content, making the most of his fun and fulfilling life as a shut-in.

It was then that Hiroaki’s world changed completely.

Dressed in his sweats, he had been lying down with his tablet held above him, when suddenly, he felt like he was falling.

“Whoa!” Hiroaki shouted in surprise. However, he hadn’t actually fallen anywhere, and was still lying on his back. The tablet in his hand hadn’t fallen, either, but the sensation against his back was strangely rugged and hard. And that wasn’t all —

For some reason, the background behind his tablet was no longer his ceiling, but a vast, clear blue sky. Hiroaki reflexively arched his neck and looked around.

“H-Huh? What’s going on?!”

Gathered right next to him were foreign-looking knights and soldiers armed with swords, spears and armor that looked they were taken straight from an outdated fantasy setting.

“Eh?!” Hiroaki sprung up, startled. While he was dressed quite foolishly, he was nothing if not utterly serious right now.

Ogling at his surroundings, a completely unfamiliar scenery stood before him. It seemed as though he was in the garden of an elegant mansion; the ground was covered in paved stone tiles, while the garden around him was filled with nature. A castle-like structure towered a little further in the distance, imposing enough to be called a palace.

The armed knights and soldiers, unfitting for the quiet and tranquil atmosphere of the garden, warily surrounded Hiroaki with a certain degree of awe.

Hey, hey... what the hell is this?! Hiroaki stood up in a panic and checked his own situation. He felt faintly more relieved to see his tablet in his left hand and his well-worn sweats on his body. However, he noticed that at some point, he had begun to clutch a European-style longsword in his grasp. It filled him with surprise and a sense of excitement.

A s-sword...? That’s a cool design... It tingles my childish heart.

But when he looked at the armed people around him, he felt a sense of wariness.

Once he had calmed down, he found the combination of the sword with his sweats to be unbearably lame, and he began to feel embarrassed too. Hiroaki tightened his grip on the sword in his hands and braced his tablet as if it were a shield.

“Ah... Umm, can you understand me? Who are all of you?” he asked, forcing down his sense of embarrassment.

A stillness fell over them... Or so Hiroaki had thought. After a moment, someone appeared from between the crowd of knights and soldiers — a cute, lavender-haired girl in her mid-teens, wearing an elegant fluttering dress.

Damn, that’s some high quality... It’s like some beautiful girl stepped straight out of a television. Is she a princess? Hiroaki thought in a daze, captivated.

Meanwhile, the lavender-haired girl took a look at Hiroaki’s appearance. Her eyes widened. After a pause, the middle-aged man next to the girl murmured something to her. Immediately after, the girl started walking toward Hiroaki with determination. The man followed, as well as two other young-looking knights. Hiroaki braced himself warily.

“U-Umm, my name is Flora. Flora Beltrum. I’m the second princess of the Kingdom of Beltrum. May I ask if you might possibly be... the hero?” she questioned nervously, having stopped at an appropriate distance from Hiroaki. For some reason, he was able to understand her words.

Hiroaki inspected the self-proclaimed princess and cocked his head in suspicion. “Hero...? Me?”

It was fishy, but it somehow matched the current situation perfectly. In fact, it was extremely similar to the prologue of the world-jumping fantasy novel he had read most recently.

Epilogue: To You, My Precious Person

One day, roughly two months after Rio and the others arrived at the spirit folk village... In the Kingdom of Beltrum — the capital of Beltrant — a young woman who looked to be in her mid teens was in the garden of the royal castle. Her name was Celia Claire: she was a count’s daughter and the youngest person to graduate from the renowned Royal Academy of Beltrum.

Celia’s long silver hair swayed in the wind as she sadly gazed at a single letter in her hands. The name Haruto was printed as the sender.

Celia knew the name; she had received a letter from a certain boy using that name once before, so she was convinced that that same boy was the one who wrote this letter, too.

The contents of the letter were straightforward and written in a familiar handwriting, stating that he would be late, but would definitely come to see her again.

“Hello, Celia... So you were here this whole time.” A man in his mid-thirties appeared, putting on airs as he spoke to Celia. The man wore elegant knight’s clothing with several medals pinned to his chest.

Celia hid the letter immediately and addressed the man — Charles Arbor — stiffly. “Sir Charles...”

Charles grinned at Celia smugly. “There’s no need to be so formal. We’ll be wedded next week, no? How about you call me ‘darling’ instead?”

“No, umm... That’s a little... It’s still a little embarrassing for me...” Celia ducked her head down and shyly bit her lip.

Charles laughed. “I do like your sense of chastity; it is lovely indeed. You even refuse to hold the hand of your fiance. I look forward to seeing how you change after our wedding.”

Goosebumps ran along Celia’s skin as she kept her head down, feigning embarrassment.

“Sir Charles, do you have a moment?” A knight suddenly appeared out of nowhere, calling for Charles.

“My, my... Just when I came to greet my adorable fiancee, work comes calling. In these times where the kingdom is in disarray, the busy duties of a large noble family never seem to cease,” Charles said, giving an exaggerated shrug of his shoulders as he expressed his disappointment.

“Everyone feels anxious without you around, Sir Charles. Please pay me no concern and go to them.” Celia gave an empty smile, trying to encourage Charles to go.

“Yes, I shall do that. I’ll come to visit you again soon, my dear.” Charles nodded in satisfaction, then turned on his heel and walked away with his subordinate.

Celia watched his retreating back and let out a deep sigh, then took the letter she had hidden away earlier back out and clutched it to her chest.

“Rio...” she whispered yearningly, on the verge of tears.